<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>#Transactions on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/%23transactions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in #Transactions on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/%23transactions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>An Article About Accounting</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/an-article-about-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/an-article-about-accounting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I was asked to write an article on Accounting. This is a VERY BROAD topic. There are also very significant differences in performing accounting for a security in receivership or a corporation or even a trust. I try to perform all the duties that I am APPOINTED to do, but this one is quite the challenge.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So I have a better idea. Let&amp;rsquo;s have an interactive thread on strictly ACCOUNTING. Ask your questions here and I will try to show you what the answers are and how you can verify them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Say That You Are 18</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/lets-say-that-you-are-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/lets-say-that-you-are-18/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ive been hinting at something in here for months, so now I will go into detail using a totally metaphorical and totally not real example. 😁&#xA;Let&amp;rsquo;s say that you are 18 and you are smarter than the rest of your high school buddies, so you opt to go to trade school rather than college. This is a GOOD DECISION! You figure that you can work as an apprentice during the day to collect your hours and go to school at night to satisfy the classroom requirements for the license that you hope to earn (yes, this is hilarious). Does everyone know how this very simple mechanism works? &amp;hellip;.good.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURETY FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/surety-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/surety-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW – SURETY FOR IDIOTS (c) 2013 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It’s been a while since I’ve posted an article, and I’ve solidified the “For Idiots” concept. Let’s cover SURETY!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the most painful things about being on FaceBook is having to endure the fact that people with chronic Dunning–Kruger effect still think that their ignorance has the same standing as my knowledge; and they will happily state many unkind things regarding my character when I challenge their “pulled-out-of-their-ass” mythology.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Show Me The Money</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/show-me-the-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/show-me-the-money/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 id=&#34;c-ingenium-holdings-incorporated-under-a-creative-commons-30-unported-license-by-nd-nc&#34;&gt;(c) INGENIUM HOLDINGS INCORPORATED under a Creative Commons 3.0 Unported License; BY-ND-NC&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you’re like me, for most of your life you’ve had minimal conscious interactions with ACCOUNTING, It was always presented to me as something very boring and complicated so I&amp;rsquo;d always avoided learning about it. While embracing my love of ignorance &lt;strong&gt;I COULD NOT SEE&lt;/strong&gt; how this &lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACTION&lt;/strong&gt; was being used against me every day or how I could use it for my benefit.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bullying 2.0</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/bullying2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/bullying2.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Prologue:  I wrote this for someone, but it may otherwise have some small value.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Bullying. Now there&amp;rsquo;s a topic. As long as there have been people who were stronger, wealthier, in more &amp;ldquo;senior&amp;rdquo; positions, better armed, meaner, dumber, less emotionally stable, there has been &amp;ldquo;bullying&amp;rdquo;. It has its own term, and there is evidence of activities that fall into this category for all of recorded history.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
