<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Story Telling on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/categories/story-telling/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Story Telling on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/categories/story-telling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Who Does The World Owe 53 Trillion Dollars To?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/who-does-the-world-owe-53-trillion-dollars-to/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/who-does-the-world-owe-53-trillion-dollars-to/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A friend asked me to write something about this, so I figured what better place to write about taxation than in this group.&#xA;What is taxation? If you use the property, isn&amp;rsquo;t it fair to pay for the usage? How can this be theft? I hope to answer these questions in the body here and in the comments if necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, you have to understand that when your parents filled out an application for a Birth Certificate, the government has to reorganize itself to account for a new organization on its books. The government has both a liability to the organization and the organization has duties owed to the government. The government borrows against the future duties in order to fulfill its obligations. Wait, what did I just say? It borrows against the future of an organization to fulfill its&amp;rsquo; duties to the organization. Yes, it saddles the organization with debt to fulfill its debt. Currently, the National Debt of the United States is almost $20 trillion. (Which shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a thing here in reality, but it is) The government is borrowing using private banks as brokers against this organizations&amp;rsquo; future which represents you. It shouldn&amp;rsquo;t take a mathematician to see the fraudulent nature of this. Of course if there was disclosure, there would be no fraud, but did any of you ever get disclosure on this? I didn&amp;rsquo;t think so&amp;hellip;..anyway&amp;hellip;.. Because there is debt in transit, which is money, a security must be issued. This security is a Bill of Lading. While the cargo is in your possession, you are liable for it. The cargo is debt. (Unfortunately, I can&amp;rsquo;t think of a simpler way to communicate this)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Dumbed Down as I Can Make It</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/as-dumbed-down-as-i-can-make-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/as-dumbed-down-as-i-can-make-it/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This isn&amp;rsquo;t easy to write because you are all begging me to come down to your level. Well, I am not at your level. I have never been an &amp;ldquo;employee&amp;rdquo;, well, as an adult, and I&amp;rsquo;ve never not had tens of thousands in Accounts Receivable in case I got into a jam. I am trying really hard to dumb it down and it&amp;rsquo;s proving to be not an easy task. You are going to have to meet me halfway. &amp;hellip;.I digress&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Be a Plumber</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/how-to-be-a-plumber/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/how-to-be-a-plumber/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;By: Chris Schulte&#xA;CC BY-ND-NC 3.0 UNPORTED LICENSE&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How to be a plumber, appointed by Ricky South&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Step one is to actually know what the fuck you are doing. There is schooling involved, trade hours, etc. [someone remind me to get back to the schooling part later please]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Step 2-4: boring plumber shit.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Step 5: what to do with the ACCOUNTING!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you work 5 days a week at $90 an hour, this should bring you in about $150k per year in labor, then maybe a little more if you mark up parts. There are expenses tied to this REVENUE that can be legally accounted against this to determine INCOME. But there&amp;rsquo;s a tax on this shit, so legally, you would want INCOME to be the lowest it could be while having enough to cover personal expenses, etc. so what options do you have?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
