<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Parasites on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/categories/parasites/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Parasites on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/categories/parasites/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hate Speech</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/hate-speech/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/hate-speech/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The title of this article is not just a title, it&amp;rsquo;s intent.  By intent, I mean that I intend to make this article qualify as &amp;ldquo;hate speech&amp;rdquo; according to every Western Law on the books.  That&amp;rsquo;s right, I intend to commit the &amp;ldquo;crime&amp;rdquo; of &amp;ldquo;hate speech&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Hate speech&amp;rdquo; is one of the invented crimes of the 1970&amp;rsquo;s.  It is one of the many LEGAL mechanisms used to suspend your critical thought.  Legally, &amp;ldquo;hate speech&amp;rdquo; is defined, but &amp;ldquo;hate&amp;rdquo; itself is not legally defined.  There&amp;rsquo;s a reason for this.  If &amp;ldquo;hate&amp;rdquo; were legally defined, even the most dull-witted reader would realize that any legislation that bore this definition, would literally be criminalizing an emotion.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Piece-of-Shit-Christians are Pieces of shit: Why Rational Discourse is Futile</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/piece-of-shit-christians-are-pieces-of-shit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/piece-of-shit-christians-are-pieces-of-shit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Did you know I&amp;rsquo;m an Ordained Minister?  It&amp;rsquo;s true.  I can legally marry people in Texas.  I&amp;rsquo;ve been to Texas twice in my life; both times I wasn&amp;rsquo;t there for more than a week.  I did, however, use my time efficiently and invested it to become an Ordained Minister of the &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;Church of the Subgenius&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; (Praise Bob!).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If you see something, say something!</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/if-you-see-something-say-something/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/if-you-see-something-say-something/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[Originally posted on Facebook, Tuesday May 3, 2016]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Have you read Aldous Huxley&amp;rsquo;s Brave New World (1932),  George Orwell&amp;rsquo;s Animal Farm (1945) and Nineteen Eighty Four (1949) , Ray Bradbury&amp;rsquo;s Fahrenheit 451 (1953), or seen the movies,  Brazil (1985) and Idiocracy (2006)?    What about books by Douglas Adams, Isaac Asimov,  Alfred Bester,  Arthur C. Clarke,  Philip K. Dick,  William Gibson,  Frank Herbert, Robert A. Heinlein,  Larry Niven,  Jerry Pournelle,  Jules Verne, H. G. Wells?   Some of you have.   It&amp;rsquo;s likely your children have not.  We have to protect our children from independent thought,  wherever possible - or so I&amp;rsquo;m told.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE TENDER FOR LAW: The Looming Threat Of FreeDumb</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/the-looming-threat-of-freedumb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/the-looming-threat-of-freedumb/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Looming Threat of FreeDumb (c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this writing I shall go further into my Noble Title, the Trust I commissioned in 1982, the Constitution, and the term ‘Freeman’.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My grandfather (John Clark Duncan) was an extraordinary man.  He was of Noble descent, and served the Royal House of Windsor in World War II, training fighter pilots and later joining the 435/436 Burma Star Squadron; where he was remembered for saving a bunch of people’s asses  (and giving somebody else the credit), and depth-charging a whale off the coast of Vancouver island.Most people are unaware of the events of 1933 and the Treaty of Westminster, a long dry, boring, convoluted document that released the subjects of the Monarchy, demoted Nobles to the status of Subject, and made all of their descendants, and current “Subjects”, Freemen.  The remaining bills granting that status were signed by John Diefenbaker in 1960, and here’s where the legal shell game begins.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
