<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>#Actors on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/%23actors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in #Actors on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/%23actors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Who’s On First: FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/whos-on-first-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/whos-on-first-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h5 id=&#34;whos-on-first-for-idiots-c-2015-roguesupport-inc-under-a-creative-commons-attribution-noncommercial-noderivs-30-unported-license&#34;&gt;Who’s On First: FOR IDIOTS (c) 2015 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For anyone still lagging behind in the “name game” confusion surrounding systems relating to law and money, I present, “Who’s on First?”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also for your edification, I have copied/pasted the opening sentences from Wikipedia describing the comedy routine, below:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Who’s on First?” is descended from turn-of-the-century burlesque sketches that used plays on words and names. Examples are “The Baker Scene” (the shop is located on Watt Street) and “Who Dyed” (the owner is named Who). In the 1930 movie Cracked Nuts, comedians Bert Wheeler and Robert Woolsey examine a map of a mythical kingdom with dialogue like this: “What is next to Which.” “What is the name of the town next to Which?” “Yes.” In English music halls (Britain’s equivalent of vaudeville theaters), comedian Will Hay performed a routine in the early 1930s (and possibly earlier) as a schoolmaster interviewing a schoolboy named Howe who came from Ware but now lives in Wye. By the early 1930s, a “Baseball Routine” had become a standard bit for burlesque comics across the United States. Abbott’s wife recalled Bud performing the routine with another comedian before teaming with Costello.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvel Jesus, Better Than Jesus, &amp; The Sermon on The Keyboard</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/marvel-jesus-better-than-jesus-and-the-sermon-on-the-keyboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/marvel-jesus-better-than-jesus-and-the-sermon-on-the-keyboard/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/bc2df4c5-c6d4-4394-9f85-b5deaf00356a&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;marvel-jesus-better-than-jesus--the-sermon-on-the-keyboard&#34;&gt;Marvel Jesus, Better Than Jesus, &amp;amp; The Sermon on The Keyboard&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Appointed by &amp;ldquo;N&amp;rdquo; for &amp;ldquo;Not Surety&amp;rdquo;,&#xA;A reference to THE TENDER FOR LAW on Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Shared under a Creative Commons 3.0 Unported License; BY-ND-NC&#xA;(c) INGENIUM HOLDINGS INCORPORATED&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I promised to handle this “thing” with the greatest care, so &amp;ldquo;what is it?&amp;rdquo; you might ask, how did I become a holder of it, and what does this stewardship mean? What does accounting have to do with the “Kingdom of God”?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
