<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JOINDER on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/categories/joinder/</link>
    <description>Recent content in JOINDER on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/categories/joinder/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Robbing a bank&#39;</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/robbing-a-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/robbing-a-bank/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ok, since there are no questions on the board, I guess everyone is on the same page here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lets discuss robbing a bank. 😀&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This post is appointed by Neens Jean. She thinks wrong and values the wrong things, but she really means to appoint this article.&#xA;You found some stranger on the internet who calls you a worthless sack of shit, but you read and what he says makes sense. How can the two points be right? Is he wrong? Well, lets find out. You are all &amp;ldquo;employees&amp;rdquo; who earn a living using this legal status. This means that you are using a security in receivership to, presumably, earn income. This is a worthless legal status because you will never gain. The administrators of the receivership will surely limit how well you do and make sure they do much better off of the deal of you working. So you are worthless. How do we steal back?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PERSONS FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/persons-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/persons-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: PERSONS FOR IDIOTS (c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All of you reading have, at one point or another, encountered the term “PERSON”.  After very little investigation, you are forced to accept the realization that you are not a PERSON, rather you HAVE a PERSON. This distinction is the first “lie of ommission” that you will encounter in the world of the “LEGAL”. THE TENDER FOR LAW axiom “LEGAL=SURETY AND ACCOUNTING” makes navigating “law” a lot simpler, and it’s very easy to spot the lies of ommission/ambiguity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGENCY (ARTIFICIAL PERSONS) FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/agency-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/agency-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: AGENCY (ARTIFICIAL PERSONS) FOR IDIOTS (c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;HER MAJESTY AND AN ORGANIZATION.  It’s the ultimate artificial person.  To understand what this means you should refer to my earlier articles.  The Criminal Code of Canada states, inter alia [Source R.S., c. C-34, s. 2 “INTERPRETATION”]:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“every one”, “person” and “owner”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;« quiconque », « individu », « personne » et « propriétaire »&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
