<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tara Duncan on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tara Duncan on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>YOU THINK WRONG, AND VALUE THE WRONG THINGS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/you-think-wrong-and-value-the-wrong-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/you-think-wrong-and-value-the-wrong-things/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: YOU THINK WRONG AND VALUE THE WRONG THINGS – By Tara Duncan (c) 2015 ROGUESUPPORT INC.  under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License. While this is predominantly directed at personal friends and acquaintances, there are perhaps some FB group members who may benefit from the information in this article, as well. This should not be new information to most. It does seem, however, to be a repeating theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our Thoughts and Prayers are With You</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/thoughts-and-prayers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/thoughts-and-prayers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;ve heard this once, you&amp;rsquo;ve heard it a hundred times. Someone is sick, in trouble, dead, struggling with some real or perceived problem&amp;hellip;you know the drill; and some well-wisher informs you that their personal, family, club, organization or social-circle&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;thoughts and prayers&amp;rdquo; are with you. You see this frequently in news articles, on social media sites, and from friends and relatives in personal conversation. You listen politely, for you are the epitome of social correctness, and thank them for their kindness. Yet, does anyone ever wonder how these thoughts and prayers might do anything for you?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Somebody Called Me A Cunt</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/somebody-called-me-a-cunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/somebody-called-me-a-cunt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Somebody called me a &amp;ldquo;cunt&amp;rdquo; once on social media. Actually to be fair more than a few people have called me this or something similar at intervals over the years; sometimes variations on this theme with greater or fewer adjectives, perhaps according to their whims, creative abilities or the occasion. This seemed dependent on their perception of how much I had offended their delicate sensibilities by simply disagreeing with whatever idea or belief they held.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We Get Phone Calls</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/we-get-phone-calls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/we-get-phone-calls/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Do you ever get those phone calls from Asian-sounding gentlemen offering assistance because your &amp;ldquo;Windows PC&amp;rdquo; is infected? They have, they say, discovered some vulnerability through their advanced internet scanning software. These kindly strangers can help you secure your machine. Some of you with more advanced computer skills (and perhaps a Windows virtual machine) may engage these people in hours of unforgettable merriment. However most of you should just hang up the phone; in the &amp;ldquo;big-shock&amp;rdquo; department this process involves giving access to your computer software, being locked out of the machine, and then &amp;ldquo;buying&amp;rdquo; the user/password information back. In short this is a malicious money-making scam. As quick cash grabs go though, it could be worse. There is an endless supply of people and organizations that exist to capitalize on the credulity of the ignorant.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Politeness vs. Political Correctness</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/politeness-vs-polticalcorrectness/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/politeness-vs-polticalcorrectness/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[Language and concepts contained herein may offend some with delicate constitutions.  If you are one of these people, please immediately stop reading]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;A dying culture invariably exhibits personal rudeness. Bad manners. Lack of consideration for others in minor matters. A loss of politeness, of gentle manners, is more significant than is a riot.” - Robert A. Heinlein, Friday&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While out with a friend, I watched as she held a door open for a passing pedestrian.  She had actually opened the door for herself, but stood back to allow an approaching man to enter the building first.  My friend is nothing if not polite.  The man, his interest firmly focused on the contents of his wireless device, sailed through the door without even looking up.  We then waited as a parade of other strangers drafted wireless guy through the door, laughing and talking amongst themselves.  Not one of them even acknowledged my friend in her new role as unpaid door person.  When the way was finally clear, my friend and I exchanged glances and moved on.  We have been having this &amp;ldquo;glance exchange&amp;rdquo; more frequently over the last few years in response to a growing number of minor, but oddly significant lapses in social etiquette exhibited by the general public.  Common courtesy is becoming uncommon.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If you see something, say something!</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/if-you-see-something-say-something/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/if-you-see-something-say-something/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[Originally posted on Facebook, Tuesday May 3, 2016]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Have you read Aldous Huxley&amp;rsquo;s Brave New World (1932),  George Orwell&amp;rsquo;s Animal Farm (1945) and Nineteen Eighty Four (1949) , Ray Bradbury&amp;rsquo;s Fahrenheit 451 (1953), or seen the movies,  Brazil (1985) and Idiocracy (2006)?    What about books by Douglas Adams, Isaac Asimov,  Alfred Bester,  Arthur C. Clarke,  Philip K. Dick,  William Gibson,  Frank Herbert, Robert A. Heinlein,  Larry Niven,  Jerry Pournelle,  Jules Verne, H. G. Wells?   Some of you have.   It&amp;rsquo;s likely your children have not.  We have to protect our children from independent thought,  wherever possible - or so I&amp;rsquo;m told.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fold.it...&#39;fold it good&#39;</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/fold-it-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/fold-it-good/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;is-this-the-fold-i-dont-know-whos-fold-this-is&#34;&gt;Is this the fold? i don&amp;rsquo;t know who&amp;rsquo;s fold this is&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[Originally published on Facebook, May 2, 2016 - I&amp;rsquo;m almost ready to try this game again :)]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As I write this a folded protein is slowly revolving, and gracefully undulating on my computer screen, while the computer program runs a constant series of simulations on how to complete and optimize the fold. Not really, that statement was utter crap. The protein depiction is just sitting there impotently in the fold.it program, as I try seemingly endless combinations of backbone manipulating, structure changing, side chain wiggling, moving and shaking, to transform this graphic representation into the folded protein of my dreams. In case the initial reference is too vague, I should mention, equally vaguely, that I&amp;rsquo;m a huge Douglas Adams fan.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just Do It</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/just-do-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 03:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/just-do-it/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I recently read an article which purports to tell you six harsh truths about yourself. It appeared to supply one &amp;ldquo;truth&amp;rdquo; in six parts, but it&amp;rsquo;s a reasonable one at least. Loosely paraphrased, it says that people who want to do something, do it. The things in question should be considered achievable, in case you&amp;rsquo;re mounting a counterpoint. So if you&amp;rsquo;re not doing that thing you love, anything else is just rhetoric.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bullying 2.0</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/bullying2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/bullying2.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Prologue:  I wrote this for someone, but it may otherwise have some small value.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Bullying. Now there&amp;rsquo;s a topic. As long as there have been people who were stronger, wealthier, in more &amp;ldquo;senior&amp;rdquo; positions, better armed, meaner, dumber, less emotionally stable, there has been &amp;ldquo;bullying&amp;rdquo;. It has its own term, and there is evidence of activities that fall into this category for all of recorded history.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
