<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>#TheRecord on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/%23therecord/</link>
    <description>Recent content in #TheRecord on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/%23therecord/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Channeling Nancy (Or; Why Lying Is Really Bad…)</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/channeling-nancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/channeling-nancy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A Tender For Law Article by Ceit Butler(c), under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am what you would describe as “an avid reader”. I started young; my grandmother had taught me to read chapter books by the time I turned 3, and in doing so she forever instilled in me a love of reading. I spent the majority of my formative years with my nose buried in a book. I read everything that I could get my hands on; comic books, encyclopedias, scientific guides, and novels. I spent days at a time exploring other worlds, as familiar with the landscapes of Narnia, Middle Earth, Olympus, and Xanth as I was with my own backyard. Visions of the future – some glorious, others terrifying – awaited me each month in the pages of Issac Asimov’s Science Fiction Magazine. I spent my nights, hiding under my blanket with flashlight in hand, wandering the dark hallways that sprang from the imagination of Lovecraft and Poe. And last, but not least, I solved mysteries alongside the likes of Sherlock Holmes, Miss Marple, and Hercule Poirot.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
