<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scott Duncan on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Scott Duncan on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LIEN YOUR NAME</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/lien-your-name/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/lien-your-name/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW – LIEN YOUR NAME (c) 2015 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Appointed by: Dan “Lien-Your-Name” Wilson&#xA;… that’s just a fancy way of saying he asked for it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’m nearing the end of my run in the public here, so I think I’ll stir the financial pot again. Today we’re going to talk about liening your name. I’ll cover the benefits, the drawbacks, and what you will actually need to do to accomplish this. Let’s start off with the basics.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOTICE OF MISTAKE</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/notice-of-mistake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/notice-of-mistake/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;(c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;notice-of-mistake--get-these-to-me-if-im-arrested&#34;&gt;NOTICE OF MISTAKE – GET THESE TO ME IF I’M ARRESTED&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;NOTICE OF MISTAKE&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;TAKE NOTICE THAT: In the matter of SURETY for the LEGAL NAME, I believe that there has been a MISTAKE, as the SOLE BENEFICIARY OF A PUBLIC DOCUMENT has been INCORRECTLY IDENTIFIED as an “accused” and/or a “suspect”.&#xA;FORGIVE ME: If I, AND/OR PERSONS AND/OR FRIENDS OF THE COURT AND/OR SUCH OTHER PARTIES ACTING IN MY INTERESTS, have led A COURT and/or STATUTORY BODY and/or A GOVERNMENT SERVICE and/or AGENTS and/or OFFICERS of such bodies, to believe, by responding to “You”, and/or “JOHN SCOTT DUNCAN”, and/or SUCH OTHER IDENTIFICATION, such bodies HAVE ADDRESSED ME AS, that I am the PARTY WITH SURETY in this matter, then that would be a MISTAKE, and please forgive me.&#xA;If I, AND/OR PERSONS AND/OR FRIENDS OF THE COURT AND/OR SUCH OTHER PARTIES ACTING IN MY INTERESTS, have led A COURT and/or STATUTORY BODY and/or A GOVERNMENT SERVICE and/or AGENTS and/or OFFICERS of such bodies, to believe, by responding to “You”, and/or “JOHN SCOTT DUNCAN”, and/or SUCH OTHER IDENTIFICATION, such bodies HAVE ADDRESSED ME AS, that I am, in ANY CAPACITY, a Pro Se litigant  and/or a LEGAL PERSON in this matter, then that would be a MISTAKE, as I DO NOT CONSENT and WAIVE THE BENEFIT to such titles (Waiver of the CHANGE OF NAMES ACT OF ONTARIO), and please forgive me.&#xA;THEREFORE: As I have no knowledge of who “You” and or “JOHN SCOTT DUNCAN” and/or SUCH OTHER IDENTIFICATION ANY COURT and/or STATUTORY BODY and/or GOVERNMENT SERVICE and/or AGENTS and/or OFFICERS of such bodies [HEREAFTER “YOU”], HAS ADDRESSED ME AS, I RESPECTFULLY ASK; by WHAT AUTHORITY ARE “YOU” ADDRESSING me as such?&#xA;As the SURETY BOND (BIRTH CERTIFICATE) has been deposited into the COURT [In the custody of Justice Wailan Low, ONTARIO SUPERIOR COURT OF JUSTICE: Court File Number CV-11-430464], WHAT EVIDENCE does the COURT have that I, as a MAN who is not lawfully entitled to the BENEFITS of a BIRTH CERTIFICATE [PPSACA13078], have any SURETY in this matter?&#xA;As GOVERNMENT is the SOLE SIGNATORY PARTY on the SURETY BOND (BIRTH CERTIFICATE), with SOLE AND FULL SURETY as TRUSTEE for the LEGAL NAME, WHAT EVIDENCE do YOU have that I am a TRUSTEE for the LEGAL NAME. WHAT EVIDENCE do YOU have that I am a TRUSTEE and have ANY SURETY with respect to ANY NAME?&#xA;WHAT EVIDENCE do YOU have, that I am an OFFICER, an AGENT, a TRUSTEE and/or an EMPLOYEE of the CROWN? WHAT EVIDENCE do “YOU” have of any WARRANT OF AGENCY for the principal?&#xA;WHAT EVIDENCE do “YOU” have that there has been any meeting of the minds, any PROPER NOTICE given, any considerable CONSIDERATION offered, or that I have ANY INTENT to CONTRACT in this matter?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PERSONS FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/persons-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/persons-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: PERSONS FOR IDIOTS (c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All of you reading have, at one point or another, encountered the term “PERSON”.  After very little investigation, you are forced to accept the realization that you are not a PERSON, rather you HAVE a PERSON. This distinction is the first “lie of ommission” that you will encounter in the world of the “LEGAL”. THE TENDER FOR LAW axiom “LEGAL=SURETY AND ACCOUNTING” makes navigating “law” a lot simpler, and it’s very easy to spot the lies of ommission/ambiguity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROPER NOTICE FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/proper-notice-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/proper-notice-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW – LIVE EXAMPLE #001 – PROPER NOTICE FOR IDIOTS (c) 2013 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&#xA;TONIGHT’S TOPIC: PROPER NOTICE&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In one of the many ongoing AQUILAE initiatives, I have cause to produce a NOTICE.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since I’m using THE TENDER FOR LAW as a notebook for my students, I figure I might as well “kill two birds with one stone” by discussing the aspects of NOTICE here, more specifically PROPER NOTICE.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURETY FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/surety-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/surety-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW – SURETY FOR IDIOTS (c) 2013 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It’s been a while since I’ve posted an article, and I’ve solidified the “For Idiots” concept. Let’s cover SURETY!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the most painful things about being on FaceBook is having to endure the fact that people with chronic Dunning–Kruger effect still think that their ignorance has the same standing as my knowledge; and they will happily state many unkind things regarding my character when I challenge their “pulled-out-of-their-ass” mythology.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGENCY (ARTIFICIAL PERSONS) FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/agency-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/agency-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: AGENCY (ARTIFICIAL PERSONS) FOR IDIOTS (c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;HER MAJESTY AND AN ORGANIZATION.  It’s the ultimate artificial person.  To understand what this means you should refer to my earlier articles.  The Criminal Code of Canada states, inter alia [Source R.S., c. C-34, s. 2 “INTERPRETATION”]:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“every one”, “person” and “owner”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;« quiconque », « individu », « personne » et « propriétaire »&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOINDER FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/joinder-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/joinder-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: JOINDER FOR IDIOTS (c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Well, spring is here.  The days are getting longer, tulips and other spring shit are showing up; I’m sure somewhere there are robins and stuff, and the FREE-DUMBERS seem to have bred and left shit-stains all over.  It’s time to do something about that.Today we are going to discuss the LEGAL NAME, the different case and spelling, and what it REALLY means.Your average FREE-DUMBER will say your capitalized name is a “CORPORATION”, and will attempt to sound smart by saying Latin phrases like, “Capitus Dickus Erectus“, or some other such nonsense that has no bearing on reality.  The case and spelling of your name is the direct result of administrative policy – and nothing more.  As many of you former fuck-wits have learned, none of this is hidden.  They must give NOTICE, so they can make their presumptions, because “ignorance of the law is no excuse”.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEGALESE FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/legalese-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/legalese-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;legalese-for-idiots&#34;&gt;LEGALESE FOR IDIOTS&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW – LEGALESE FOR IDIOTS (c) 2013 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It’s feast or famine around here at THE TENDER FOR LAW. This is article number two in as many days!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Derek Moran says that he finds it difficult to believe that I will be able to top the SURETY article…CHALLENGE ACCEPTED.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is almost midnight on Sunday, I’m on the bridge of the Tycho-Brahe, and as I look out onto the lake the water is like a sheet of glass…and it’s not even frozen. How can I not produce a superior article tonight? So today, with all my “God” complex, “arrogance”, and the knowledge that a host of “pseudo radio” is reading my superior work, and knowing that all he can do is tremble in impotent fury. Things are so good I can cover the bad aspects of law, namely its language.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSURANCE FOR THE INEPT</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/insurance-for-the-inept/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/insurance-for-the-inept/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW – APPOINTED ARTICLE – INSURANCE FOR THE INEPT – By APPOINTMENT of Gail Blackman (c) 2013 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the great things about being in a law forum, run by a prorogued noble, is that you have the unique opportunity of posing the right question and always getting a near-magical answer; which causes something to flip in that little lump of protoplasm you laughingly call a brain.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Is The Difference Between LEGAL And LAWFUL?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/what-is-the-diffrence-between-legal-and-lawful/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/what-is-the-diffrence-between-legal-and-lawful/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What is the difference between LEGAL and LAWFUL?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To answer this question one must first answer the question, “What is LAW?”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Social conditioning and the public discourse of lawyers is intentionally designed to stop you from asking this question.  Here in reality there have been many attempts to define it.  Law is just a weasel-word catch-phrase, like “Due Process“. It doesn’t actually exist.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIES AND THE LYING LIARS WHO LIE ABOUT THE LIES THEY TELL</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/lies-and-lying-liars-who-lie-about-the-liaes-they-tell/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/lies-and-lying-liars-who-lie-about-the-liaes-they-tell/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;lies-and-the-lying-liars-who-lie-about-the-lies-they-tell-an-objective-and-fair-analysis-of-the-law-society&#34;&gt;LIES AND THE LYING LIARS WHO LIE ABOUT THE LIES THEY TELL: An Objective and Fair Analysis of the LAW SOCIETY&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: LIES AND THE LYING LIARS WHO LIE ABOUT THE LIES THEY TELL: An Objective and Fair Analysis of the LAW SOCIETY (c) 2016 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As of this writing the Roguesupport Initiative, THE TENDER FOR LAW, is 3.75 years old. The project was started on FaceBook for numerous reasons, one of which was that it meets the LEGAL burden of “PUBLIC RECORD”. In theory, what I write on Facebook could be read by over one billion people. Here in reality, that’s not very likely, but it’s also not very likely that you ever went to the classified ads in the newspaper intentionally looking for “LEGAL NOTICES”, either. It doesn’t matter if people read the notice, it simply has to be “made available” in a manner that one could reasonably access. It’s not difficult to go to your public library and look up the contents of an old newspaper. It’s even easier to obtain a Facebook account. The “LEGAL BURDEN” has been met.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obiter Dictum: MEADS V. MEADS FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/obiter-dictum-meades-v-meads-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/obiter-dictum-meades-v-meads-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;obiter-dictum-meads-v-meads-for-idiots&#34;&gt;Obiter Dictum: MEADS V. MEADS FOR IDIOTS&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: Obiter dictum: MEADS v. MEADS FOR IDIOTS (c) 2015 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It’s time to stir the pot – disturb some shit as it were, stoke the fire, prime the forge, enrich uranium in a centrifuge, shit like that. In order to accomplish this noble goal I’m going to do something that, on the surface, seems disgusting. I’m going to arm the FREE-DUMBERS WITH THE KNOWLEDGE TO CRUSH MEADS V. MEADS. If you’re really lucky, I’ll try to squeeze in some “Nazis” too. If this seems a little “rushed, it’s because this was published BY APPOINTMENT!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DUSTIN MYHEAD</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/dustin-myhead/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/dustin-myhead/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It is the story of &amp;ldquo;Dustin&amp;rdquo;. Full name:&#xA;Dustin MyHead.&#xA;Posted originally BY: Scott Duncan, April 14, 2016 · Toronto, ON, Canada on Facebook.&#xA;(c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons&#xA;Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&#xA;People from the Kook-Of-Gaia camp are starting to bleed into my realm. I mistakenly&#xA;answered a question in a post on my page, and a Kook-Of-Gaia piss-guzzling&#xA;FREE-DUMBER started throwing around FREE-DUMB terminology and using words which&#xA;he demonstrably doesn&amp;rsquo;t understand. So, it appears I must dumb myself down even further,&#xA;because Kook-Of-Gaia has a lot of ignorance to account for. I&amp;rsquo;m going to do this by telling a&#xA;children&amp;rsquo;s story:&#xA;It is the story of &amp;ldquo;Dustin&amp;rdquo;. Full name: Dustin MyHead. Dustin&amp;rsquo;s story is very important&#xA;because it&amp;rsquo;s your story too. Thus, you should pay close attention to it.&#xA;Dustin was born with a silver spoon in his mouth, as is everybody in the Western world who&#xA;has a standard of living better than 98% of the world&amp;rsquo;s population. This means Dustin was&#xA;born rich, and powerful. Dustin was so rich and powerful, in fact, that people addressed him&#xA;as MASTER.&#xA;As a child in this privileged world, Dustin had many servants - the maids, the butlers, the&#xA;groundskeepers, and the janitors - who did the jobs they were paid to, to ensure that Dustin&#xA;had everything to which his wealth and power entitled him. As the years passed and Dustin&#xA;grew, the maids and butlers saw to his every need, so much so, that he realized he had&#xA;begun to rely on the maids and butlers to do everything. Dustin didn&amp;rsquo;t like the idea of being&#xA;dependent on paid strangers to see to his day-to-day needs; so one day Dustin woke up, got&#xA;out of bed, and went down to that room where only the servants seem to go. His goal was to&#xA;learn how to do his own laundry. The machine sat there. It looked simple, and clean, and&#xA;elegant, but the machine had pictures and words on it he didn&amp;rsquo;t understand. He then realized&#xA;he needed to consult an expert to instruct him on this task. He asked the servant who does&#xA;his laundry, how the machine works. Instead of answering his question, his servant actively&#xA;discouraged him from learning, even though it was his fucking washing machine. &amp;ldquo;A man of&#xA;your status doesn&amp;rsquo;t do manual labour like that. It&amp;rsquo;s just not proper. Leave the laundry to me,&amp;rdquo;&#xA;she said.&#xA;Dustin replied, &amp;ldquo;But I own this washing machine. It is my property and it is indisputably&#xA;mine.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Oh sir, nobody is contesting that,&amp;rdquo; she replied, &amp;ldquo;But you are rich and powerful, and the time&#xA;it would take to learn to use this silly device is far beneath you and would be a waste of yourprecious time. You&amp;rsquo;re rich and powerful. Your time is important. Mine is not. So give up this&#xA;silly idea of learning how the machine works.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Dustin set out to learn how to accomplish other tasks, but ran into the same opposition with&#xA;every skill he tried to acquire. The cooks wouldn&amp;rsquo;t allow him to cook in his own kitchen. He&#xA;might burn himself. The security guards wouldn&amp;rsquo;t let him learn to properly use a firearm to&#xA;defend himself, warning him, &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;ll put your eye out!&amp;rdquo; The gardener carefully explained how&#xA;dangerous the equipment is, and how somebody as important as Dustin shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be&#xA;exposed to such peril.&#xA;One day Dustin asked, &amp;ldquo;If I&amp;rsquo;m the master, why aren&amp;rsquo;t you doing what I ask of you?&amp;rdquo;&#xA;His staff responded, &amp;ldquo;Well if we did that, we&amp;rsquo;d lose our jobs. The security guard would&#xA;definitely lose his job if you put your eye out. The gardener would certainly lose his job if you&#xA;injured yourself using the equipment. Even the maid would lose her job if your laundry piled&#xA;up because the washing machine was broken.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;Dustin asked, &amp;ldquo;Who else could decide you lose your job if I&amp;rsquo;m the master?&amp;rdquo;&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Why the accountant does,&amp;rdquo; they replied.&#xA;To solve this mystery, Dustin went to see his estate&amp;rsquo;s accountant, and asked, &amp;ldquo;None of my&#xA;servants are doing what I tell them. What the fuck?&amp;rdquo;&#xA;With infinite patience, the accountant set out to explain to Dustin, what the fuck was the fuck.&#xA;He explained that all of this takes money to run, and while money used to be an economic&#xA;measure of one&amp;rsquo;s labour, it is now &amp;ldquo;debt in transit&amp;rdquo;. There is SURETY and ACCOUNTING&#xA;attached to that money - and that&amp;rsquo;s the price you pay for being rich and powerful in a&#xA;RECEIVERSHIP. Dustin was confused by this, and went back and did what he always did&#xA;when he was confused. He prayed to a mutilated man, while drinking his own piss. Years&#xA;passed because Dustin listened to Kook-Of-Gaia and believes in FREE-DUMB bullshit, while&#xA;not knowing anything about the world around him.&#xA;Everywhere in the British Commonwealth since 1933, the CROWN has been a RECEIVER.&#xA;When that happened, Princess Elizabeth gave up her BIRTH RIGHT, and freed all her&#xA;SUBJECTS, in order to pay for the upcoming war. In COMMON LAW JURISDICTIONS that&#xA;ESTATE is your BIRTH RIGHT. The woman you idiots think is a lizard is the one responsible&#xA;for the debt. That&amp;rsquo;s why LEGALLY there is only one SOVEREIGN, because LEGALLY,&#xA;SOVEREIGNS take ORDERS. She takes the ORDERS, so you don&amp;rsquo;t have to - and for nearly&#xA;fifty years it worked beautifully, right up to around the time Scott Duncan was born - which is&#xA;coincidentally pretty much when everything went sideways, although no one knew it at the&#xA;time.&#xA;&amp;hellip;but I digress.&#xA;Let&amp;rsquo;s get back to Dustin. The years passed and Dustin became more, and more, inept and&#xA;helpless. His servants were now telling him where he could go in the house, and where hecouldn&amp;rsquo;t. He wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure when this had happened, but he didn&amp;rsquo;t like what his life had become.&#xA;One day, he tried to defy one of the servants, and the servant called the security guard. In a&#xA;blatant violation of Dustin&amp;rsquo;s RIGHTS, in Dustin&amp;rsquo;s property, on Dustin&amp;rsquo;s estate, a security&#xA;guard whom Dustin employed, physically dragged him out of his own property. Dustin&#xA;stormed over to the accountant to have the man fired, but the accountant said, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m sorry, I&#xA;no longer have that power, because we&amp;rsquo;re in CANADA, and since the UK CANADA ACT&#xA;(1982), the lawyers have the final say regarding which servants can be fired.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;But I&amp;rsquo;m the MASTER,&amp;rdquo; replied Dustin, &amp;ldquo;The MASTER has the final say!&amp;rdquo;&#xA;The accountant assured him, &amp;ldquo;While that&amp;rsquo;s true, the stooge in a black dress with an ARTS&#xA;degree says it isn&amp;rsquo;t; and since we signed the CHARTER he has the final say.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;&amp;ldquo;But I didn&amp;rsquo;t sign any CHARTER&amp;rdquo; said Dustin.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;No&amp;rdquo;, continued the accountant, &amp;ldquo;But you did use money, and in doing so you ACCEPTED a&#xA;TENDER FOR LAW.&amp;rdquo;&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Well you&amp;rsquo;re my accountant, why didn&amp;rsquo;t you tell me that?&amp;rdquo; asked Dustin.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s none of your business how I run my accounting firm. It&amp;rsquo;s not my job to tell you. You&#xA;should have learned yourself; and on your eighteenth birthday, I owe you diddly squat,&amp;rdquo; was&#xA;the reply. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m an accountant. I know what money is. I have to, to do my job. That&amp;rsquo;s why I get&#xA;to set PUBLIC POLICY, and you don&amp;rsquo;t. If you don&amp;rsquo;t like it, ask the guy in the black dress with&#xA;the ARTS degree. Because that&amp;rsquo;s reality, Dustin. I&amp;rsquo;ll grant you that all your servants&#xA;discouraged you from learning, but now you can&amp;rsquo;t do anything without them. You have no&#xA;VALUE, and now the servants are in charge. You sold us your BIRTH RIGHT, and you pay&#xA;for it with your hubris and ignorance. Yes, we&amp;rsquo;re all collectively exploiting your BIRTH RIGHT,&#xA;but we&amp;rsquo;re GOVERNMENT. &amp;quot;&#xA;We&amp;rsquo;re all GOVERNMENT,&amp;rdquo; said the man in the black dress with the ARTS degree. &amp;ldquo;I have no&#xA;idea how a computer works,&amp;rdquo; he says, &amp;ldquo;but I have the RIGHT to say you don&amp;rsquo;t get to learn&#xA;either. Don&amp;rsquo;t you know my ARTS degree is in lying? I have mastered it, and if I don&amp;rsquo;t like the&#xA;PUBLIC POLICY the accountant is setting, I can just change the meaning of some words.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m just PRACTICING my art. All because you used money. You chose hubris and ignorance&#xA;because you didn&amp;rsquo;t value what was most important, and you gave it up without a fight. We&amp;rsquo;ll&#xA;let you walk around with the title of MASTER, and we&amp;rsquo;ll continue to pretend to serve you.&#xA;But, MASTER Dustin, it&amp;rsquo;s all SURETY and ACCOUNTING now. You don&amp;rsquo;t own anything, and&#xA;you don&amp;rsquo;t have the RIGHT to anything. Your parents gave us permission to do this. We have&#xA;their signature right here, and you don&amp;rsquo;t have any LEGAL RIGHTS until you&amp;rsquo;re eighteen. Did&#xA;you LIEN your name before you used it? Why do you think banks won&amp;rsquo;t normally give a&#xA;MORTGAGE to somebody who has LIENED their name? The LIEN itself means they have&#xA;absolutely no LEGAL obligation to pay the debt, which means the banks must TRUST you&#xA;implicitly to loan you money - and they&amp;rsquo;ll only do that if you have VALUE to offer. Here, the&#xA;man in the black dress patted little Dustin condescendingly on the head, and said, &amp;ldquo;See?&#xA;There&amp;rsquo;s no FRAUD. You&amp;rsquo;re just a stupid, ignorant entitled Fuck&amp;hellip;and you&amp;rsquo;re getting what you&#xA;deserve. While you are cutting your dicks off, and drinking your own piss and yelling,&amp;ldquo;FREEDUMMMMMBBB,&amp;rdquo; we&amp;rsquo;d really appreciate it if you sold us your children as well. That&#xA;lucky baby will be born owing about $30,000.00. Since money is DEBT in TRANSIT, we can&#xA;take that money, bundle it as a SECURITY and sell it on the open market - with the promise&#xA;that the thing that crawled out of the vagina of the woman stupid enough to let you stick your&#xA;dick in it, will pay it back. Blame your parents for being as ignorant and full of hubris as you&#xA;are, Dustin, because now we can drop all pretence. The servants are in charge now. Your&#xA;parents spent money they didn&amp;rsquo;t have, and stuck you with the BILL. We intend to collect.&#xA;LEGALLY we must give all the NOTICES necessary, and we do,&amp;rdquo; said the man in the black&#xA;dress with the ARTS degree. Thanks to your hubris and ignorance, we&amp;rsquo;re in charge now, and&#xA;you&amp;rsquo;re going to pay your share of the BILL. Until that BILL is PAID, you have no&#xA;AUTHORITY. So do your job, create new money that will go into our pockets, instead of&#xA;paying down the DEBT. Since the time of Shakespeare, you arrogant idiots make&#xA;DECLARATIONS using words for which you don&amp;rsquo;t know the definition. When you&amp;rsquo;re dealing&#xA;with money, it&amp;rsquo;s always LEGAL. That&amp;rsquo;s the only definition that counts. The same is true with&#xA;courts. Only the LEGAL definitions matter. It&amp;rsquo;s especially true with ACCOUNTING. LEGAL is&#xA;the LAW of SURETY AND ACCOUNTING. &amp;quot;&#xA;Dustin looked up at the odious man in the black dress with the ARTS degree, and finally&#xA;realized he was looking at evil. So he asked, &amp;ldquo;I know you&amp;rsquo;re evil in its purest form. So why&#xA;are you telling me this?&amp;rdquo;&#xA;The evil man in the black dress looked into Dustin&amp;rsquo;s ignorant eyes, and answered, &amp;ldquo;I was&#xA;kicked out of the club for daring to ask, &amp;lsquo;Have we the RIGHT?&amp;rdquo; He then proceeded to piss in&#xA;Dustin&amp;rsquo;s mouth, &amp;ldquo;Because fuck you, you stupid little shit!&amp;rdquo; (Quite the plot twist, huh? Bet you&#xA;didn&amp;rsquo;t see that one coming.) This is why being an actual scientist is better, because a &amp;ldquo;law&#xA;degree&amp;rdquo; and a &amp;ldquo;gender studies&amp;rsquo; degree have the same worth: NOTHING. It&amp;rsquo;s all BELIEF.&#xA;And this story is more accurate to reality than all of the stupid bullshit Kook-of-Gaia ever&#xA;said.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m Not Authorized To Answer Questions</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/im-not-authorized-to-answer-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/im-not-authorized-to-answer-questions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You will need this soon, and it may save your life, so PAY ATTENTION.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;IF YOU ARE ARRESTED: You DO NOT TALK TO POLICE, and NEVER ANSWER QUESTIONS. If they say &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rsquo;re under arrest&amp;rdquo;, you don&amp;rsquo;t answer ANY question. Even if it sounds &amp;ldquo;innocent&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Police give NOTICE: In United States they say &amp;ldquo;You are under arrest for &lt;em&gt;Insert made-up bullshit here&lt;/em&gt;. You have the right to remain silent, and ANYTHING you say may (That means &amp;ldquo;will&amp;rdquo;) be used AGAINST YOU (Notice not HELP you) in a court of law. You have the right to an attorney&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; followed by bullshit you should ignore. DO NOT let ANYONE act on your behalf.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THERE ARE NO GIRLS ON THE INTERNET</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/no-girls-on-the-interent/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/no-girls-on-the-interent/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;THERE ARE NO GIRLS ON THE INTERNET&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before we get to the post, a little history; Half of this will sound familiar because it&amp;rsquo;s an Internet meme! You can look it up!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;@TaraDuncan knows herself, with absolute certainty, that the history on the public record is made-up bullshit, because She took dictation when the first half was done. That&amp;rsquo;s right, it was stripped of its point/counterpoint context, and only my half was posted&amp;hellip;years after this.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eliminating Disease</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/eliminating-disease/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/eliminating-disease/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Scott Duncan - Vice President; Rogue Support Inc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Unless you have literally been living on another planet, it is an absolute certainty you&amp;rsquo;ve heard the term, &amp;ldquo;COVID-19&amp;rdquo;. Throughout this imaginary crisis I have made declarations that later turned out to be true. I know most of you hate facts, reason and knowledge, and say I&amp;rsquo;m a really bad person for daring to speak out against the &amp;ldquo;expert&amp;rdquo; opinions of our substitute drama teacher Prime Minister&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Irish Rocco</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/irish-rocco/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/irish-rocco/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;irish-rocco&#34;&gt;IRISH ROCCO!&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So @DaveCullen plays the naive &amp;ldquo;useful idiot&amp;rsquo; and sets you all up for a fleecing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.minds.com/newsfeed/1141794890200764416&#34;&gt;https://www.minds.com/newsfeed/1141794890200764416&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How? Well let&amp;rsquo;s walk through it, shall we?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m going to sound like a broken record here, but you don&amp;rsquo;t actually listen to the axioms you affectionately call &amp;ldquo;Scottisms&amp;rdquo;. You&amp;rsquo;ll hear the words, and you&amp;rsquo;ll comprehend their meaning. Like many of the things I tell you, when you hear them you know they&amp;rsquo;re true. When reminded, you&amp;rsquo;ll nod sagely in the knowledge you have this useful information. Time will pass, and you&amp;rsquo;ll need to be reminded again.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Prodigal Son</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/the-prodigal-son/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/the-prodigal-son/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A few words on the subject of being right.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My name is Scott Duncan.  I am trusted with a lot of secrets, and I keep those secrets by being honest.  It&amp;rsquo;s counter-intuitive, but it works profoundly well.  I write on these relatively obscure mediums which, while public, aren&amp;rsquo;t actively promoted.  This is by design.  Only those who have been following me for the past four years will truly understand what I&amp;rsquo;m saying here; and the rest of you, of course, will misinterpret it.  Know that any action that you take based on that misinterpretation, is by design.  I fully expect you to do the wrong thing, based on the wrong perception, and when you do, that makes you my servant.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hate Speech</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/hate-speech/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/hate-speech/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The title of this article is not just a title, it&amp;rsquo;s intent.  By intent, I mean that I intend to make this article qualify as &amp;ldquo;hate speech&amp;rdquo; according to every Western Law on the books.  That&amp;rsquo;s right, I intend to commit the &amp;ldquo;crime&amp;rdquo; of &amp;ldquo;hate speech&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Hate speech&amp;rdquo; is one of the invented crimes of the 1970&amp;rsquo;s.  It is one of the many LEGAL mechanisms used to suspend your critical thought.  Legally, &amp;ldquo;hate speech&amp;rdquo; is defined, but &amp;ldquo;hate&amp;rdquo; itself is not legally defined.  There&amp;rsquo;s a reason for this.  If &amp;ldquo;hate&amp;rdquo; were legally defined, even the most dull-witted reader would realize that any legislation that bore this definition, would literally be criminalizing an emotion.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Piece-of-Shit-Christians are Pieces of shit: Why Rational Discourse is Futile</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/piece-of-shit-christians-are-pieces-of-shit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/piece-of-shit-christians-are-pieces-of-shit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Did you know I&amp;rsquo;m an Ordained Minister?  It&amp;rsquo;s true.  I can legally marry people in Texas.  I&amp;rsquo;ve been to Texas twice in my life; both times I wasn&amp;rsquo;t there for more than a week.  I did, however, use my time efficiently and invested it to become an Ordained Minister of the &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;Church of the Subgenius&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; (Praise Bob!).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Truth About The Illuminati Or Why Piece-Of-Shit Christians Are Such Pieces-Of-Shit</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/or-why-piece-of-shit-chistiansare-such-pieces-of-shit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/or-why-piece-of-shit-chistiansare-such-pieces-of-shit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Shared under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;SCOTT DUNCAN·WEDNESDAY, 21 OCTOBER 2015&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Piece-of-Shit Christians” – you hear me say it a lot. I say it so much, and I’ve been saying it for so long, that the prefix “Piece-of-Shit” is automatically inserted in front of it, each and every time I hear the word “Christian”. This is much like the experience of Elliot in “Mr. Robot” with “Evil Corp”. (I also find myself mentally apologizing to Claudia Christian every time I think of her. Shit…there I go again! Sorry Claudia. :/)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFAMATORY LIBEL FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/defamatory-libel-for-odiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/defamatory-libel-for-odiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-tender-for-law-defamatory-libel-for-idiots-a-serendipitously-happily-coincidental-article-c-1982-2015-roguesupport-inc-under-a-creative-commons-attribution-noncommercial-noderivs-30-unported-license&#34;&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: DEFAMATORY LIBEL FOR IDIOTS; A Serendipitously, Happily-Coincidental Article (c) 1982-2015 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In case none of you read that LICENSE, that means that no COMMERCE is expected and/or IMPLIED…again, in case you are confused.  Only members of THE TENDER FOR LAW will understand why that’s so important.  ALSO: there are no “answers” here, just a “setting of the scene” as it were…&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CORPUS DELICTI</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/corpus-dilecti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/corpus-dilecti/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:1313/img/murder.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;CORPUS DELICTI&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: PERSONS FOR IDIOTS (c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“CORPUS DELICTI” The MOST IGNORED LEGAL CONCEPT!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The circle-jerkers at Quatloos have been scouring the 1960 CANADIAN BILL OF RIGHTS for what is supposedly my own “crazy” position that for a CRIME, there must be an INJURED PARTY. They LOVE cherry-picking, or just plain ignoring the maxim of CORPUS DELICTI! Even their precious “Justices” agree with me!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Give In Lieu Of “Identification”</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/given-in-leiu-of-identification/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/given-in-leiu-of-identification/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;give-in-lieu-of-identification&#34;&gt;Give In Lieu Of “Identification”&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;NOTICE OF WAIVER OF PUBLIC BENEFITS (ONTARIO CHANGE OF NAME ACT  [R.S.O. 1990, CHAPTER C.7])&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;WHEREAS YOU, being a PUBLIC SERVANT and/or an OFFICER for a PUBLIC TRUST, and/or A GOVERNMENT AGENT/OFFICIAL, have demanded “IDENTIFICATION” from ME, and&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;WHEREAS YOU, being a PUBLIC SERVANT and/or an OFFICER for a PUBLIC TRUST, and/or A GOVERNMENT AGENT/OFFICIAL, do NOT have the right, and/or AUTHORITY, to attach SURETY and/or JOINDER, to ANY NAME DERIVED FROM A PUBLIC DOCUMENT, and attach such NAME and/or JOINDER to ME, and&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT’S ALL NATURAL!</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/its-all-natural/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/its-all-natural/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;26 June 2014 at 20:40&#xA;You often hear me lament the fact that there are people who only pretend to think.  I often counter this unfortunate phenomenon with Tim Minchin’s “Storm”.   More specifically, I reference the quote “Do you know what they call alternative medicine that’s been proven to work?  …medicine”.   The alternative medicine crowd has no idea what this means, as they consider PhotoShop pictures and Youtube videos “proof”.  They try to look “sciency”, but rarely have anything resembling proof, while always seeming to have a “store”.  This, in and of itself, should make you suspicious about the self-serving nature of anything being recommended, but the larger issue is with the process itself.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Libertarians and My Cat</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/libertarians-and-my-cat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/libertarians-and-my-cat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;libertarians-and-my-cat&#34;&gt;Libertarians And My Cat&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: Libertarians and my cat. (c) 2015  ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Figure 1: This is Meko and Trouble. They are cats&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Figure 2: This is Larken Rose. He is a Libertarian. He recently said:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“There are plenty of different legalese mythology theories which amount to, “You accidentally and secretly AGREED and CONSENTED to be ruled by government by…” Then they end the statement with “calling yourself a ‘citizen&amp;rsquo;” or “using FRN’s” or “having a Social Security Number” or “using a bank account” or “spelling your name in all capital letters” or they say it’s about living here without filing some magic piece of paper or “declaring” something or other.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Belief Is My Conviction</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/my-belief-is-my-conviction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/my-belief-is-my-conviction/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: “MY BELIEF, IS MY CONVICTION”&#xA;(c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&#xA;I was talking to the man who once fleetingly served as helmsman of the Tycho-Brahe (known to the world as “The Fender”), heady from his pseudo-victory of seeing a legal connection that I didn’t. He decided to take a run at my ultimate CONVICTION; ALL belief is EVIL.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’ll continue with my story, but first I want to point out (as usual) how ignorant you are. I know that really hurts your feelings, but it doesn’t make it any less true. I will not continue my story until I convince you of this fact (you ignorant fuck!).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oh Say Can&#39;t You See?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/a-primer-on-citizenship/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/a-primer-on-citizenship/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;oh-say-cant-you-see--a-primer-on-citizenship&#34;&gt;OH, SAY CAN’T YOU SEE? – A Primer On Citizenship&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: “OH, SAY CAN’T YOU SEE? – A Primer on Citizenship” (c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&#xA;In one of our many lively discussions, on the many lively forums that my captains and I chat in and/or frequent, the erstwhile Captain Wentz revealed a small but interesting factoid that surprised a few people;  He pointed out that from 1992 to 2002, he was in fact, the Admiral of the AQUILAE Navy.  I spent most of those years as a specialist and/or non-commissioned officer.  That’s right, for a while I was “Scotty” in the engine room.  The reason I’m not doing it today (despite how much I enjoyed it), is that I don’t think I could endure everyone who meets me, making a “Scotty in the engine room joke”, followed by a strange smug demeanour, like he/she was the first one to ever come up with a “Scotty in the fucking Engine Room” joke.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OMNIJURISDICTIONAL NOTICE</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/omnijurisdictional-notice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/omnijurisdictional-notice/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;omnijurisdictional-notice&#34;&gt;OMNIJURISDICTIONAL NOTICE&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: AN OMNIJURISDICTIONAL NOTICE (c) 1982-2015 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;NOTICE: This document will KEEP GROWING. CONTENT ADDED DAILY TO THIS NOTE!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ATTENTION, SIMU-DRONES:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It’s 2015. Things are getting darker, but you are getting smarter. You see now, or at least grasp, how to gain wealth and power, but you are at a loss as to what to do with it if you succeed. I have GREAT news! Now you have an answer! WAR!  LET’S PRACTICE!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONE TRILLION DOLLARS!</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/one-trillion-dollars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/one-trillion-dollars/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;one-trillion-dollars&#34;&gt;ONE TRILLION DOLLARS!&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(c) 2016 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jan 28th 2016:  Scott Duncan shared Jamie Redman‘s post&#xA;HEY! Andrew D’Spyder-Pig! Looks like those evil Bitcoin folk have “thefted” a trillion bucks! 😀&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Imagine that. The awesome Satoshi Nakamoto has engineered something that “Stole” a trillion dollars, and proved the viability of the Blockchain. The entire future has been re-written, and the technologies that sprung from it, are here to stay.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paperwork Terroism!</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/paperwork-terrorism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/paperwork-terrorism/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t know if any of you have read this bill, C-16, and the terrifying ramifications contained therein; but if you haven&amp;rsquo;t you really should, even if you&amp;rsquo;re not in Canada.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As this &amp;ldquo;law&amp;rdquo; is currently framed, my satirical recreation of a &amp;ldquo;Gender Fluid&amp;rdquo; PSA would be a crime in Canada, for which I could be jailed.  If you think I&amp;rsquo;m being alarmist, I remind you that people have been sentenced to multiple years in prison, simply for publishing the INTENT to publish, a book questioning the Holocaust.  This happens in Germany right now.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putting It All Together</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/putting-it-all-together/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/putting-it-all-together/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(c) 2013 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In THE TENDER FOR LAW&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;one of its evolved Maxims is that “The gold is in the comments”. This is true for me too, as it allows me to gauge just how much you are assimilating. Every once in a while though, a “gold nugget” comes up for me. This is no easy task, and the scarcity of this gold makes it far more valuable to me than it is to you. The question I reference came up unexpectedly and related to an incredulous observation regarding the product of my three years’ of giving actual answers and actual solutions, and telling the actual truth (all of which can be verified by the passage of time). This erstwhile interrogator asked, “Why aren’t millions of people here?”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE TENDER FOR LAW – CHILDREN’S AID SOCIETY [C.A.S] FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/childrens-aid-society-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/childrens-aid-society-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;(c) 2013 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article is what we like to call an “emergency article” in as much as Dean Clifford has publicly and blatantly lied about family services and the law. Before we get started we are going to refer to the JURISDICTION I am most familiar with. You will find mirrors of this in any JURISDICTION that uses a world reserve currency.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE TENDER FOR LAW: The Looming Threat Of FreeDumb</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/the-looming-threat-of-freedumb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/the-looming-threat-of-freedumb/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Looming Threat of FreeDumb (c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this writing I shall go further into my Noble Title, the Trust I commissioned in 1982, the Constitution, and the term ‘Freeman’.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My grandfather (John Clark Duncan) was an extraordinary man.  He was of Noble descent, and served the Royal House of Windsor in World War II, training fighter pilots and later joining the 435/436 Burma Star Squadron; where he was remembered for saving a bunch of people’s asses  (and giving somebody else the credit), and depth-charging a whale off the coast of Vancouver island.Most people are unaware of the events of 1933 and the Treaty of Westminster, a long dry, boring, convoluted document that released the subjects of the Monarchy, demoted Nobles to the status of Subject, and made all of their descendants, and current “Subjects”, Freemen.  The remaining bills granting that status were signed by John Diefenbaker in 1960, and here’s where the legal shell game begins.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE TENDER FOR LAW: The Looming Threat Of FreeDumb – ADDENDUM</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/the-looming-threat-of-freedumb-addendum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/the-looming-threat-of-freedumb-addendum/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: The Looming Threat of FreeDumb – ADDENDUM (c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License. ADDENDUM TO [ https://www.facebook.com/notes/scott-duncan/the-tender-for-law-the-looming-threat-of-freedumb/815869621812845 ]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I received a message from a woman today that filled me with both anger and despair.  As you may have guessed, I justifiably hold all of you in the highest contempt.  Often I find myself longing for the mindset and ethical structure (or lack thereof) that would allow me to take my many extraordinary abilities, and just kill you all.  I won’t lie to you…it’s not for your safety, it’s for mine.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE-DUMB – THE TRUTH &amp; ROBERT MENARD</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/freedumb-the-truth-and-robert-menard/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/freedumb-the-truth-and-robert-menard/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW – Pseudo-article-to-tide-you-over-while-we-continue-work on-the-next-article:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;…OK, not really. Roll the copyright and licence!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;( Shut up! It’s coming! )&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the super-secret group, THE TENDER FOR LAW (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/groups/tenderforlaw/)&#34;&gt;https://www.facebook.com/groups/tenderforlaw/)&lt;/a&gt;, I was asked a very interesting question regarding how soon one of my “predictions” will come to pass.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Those that have come to know me recently, and/or those who have known me for a longer period (20 years or more), can all agree on one thing; I see shit coming, and I understand substantially more than everyone else.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONE PEOPLE’S PUBLIC FRAUD (OPPF) Part TWO: The UCC For Idiots</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/oppf-p2-ucc-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/oppf-p2-ucc-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;one-peoples-public-fraud-oppf-part-two-the-ucc-for-idiots&#34;&gt;ONE PEOPLE’S PUBLIC FRAUD (OPPF) Part TWO: The UCC For Idiots&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ORIGINALLY PUBLISHED on 24 February 2013 · in THE TENDER FOR LAW: ONE PEOPLE’S PUBLIC FRAUD (OPPF) Part TWO: The UCC for Idiots (c) 2013 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&#xA;As promised, I am now going to cover the UNIFORM COMMERCIAL CODE (or UCC, for you idiots who type with your thumbs.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;FUCK! Myths about THIS shit, sure has “done the rounds”, hasn’t it? No more myths have been generated, out of a piece of regulation, than the UNIFORM COMMERCIAL CODE!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONE PEOPLE’S PUBLIC FRAUD (OPPF) Part ONE</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/oppf-p1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/oppf-p1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ORIGINALLY PUBLISHED on 23 February 2013 · in THE TENDER FOR LAW:ONE PEOPLE’S PUBLIC FRAUD (OPPF) Part ONE (c) 2013 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ONE PEOPLE’S PUBLIC FRAUD (OPPF) …You’ll notice I didn’t use the word TRUST.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Scams like this diminish the word in much the same way GOVERNMENTS have diminished the words “human rights”.  As this is my forum, I think I will prevent the concept of TRUSTS being diminished any further by this scam.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
