<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Various Authors on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Various Authors on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Those Who Mistrust</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/those-who-mis-trust/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/those-who-mis-trust/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The title of this paper is a little tricky. We’ll just clarify at the outset that those who mistrust— miss trusts. Those who mistrust are those who make a serious mistake. What I will be discussing is the mistake of missing the point about Express Trusts and the advantages of using Express Trusts wisely.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To illustrate I will tell you about a peculiar case I worked on in 2002 with an attorney who contacted me on a recommendation from the attorney who I actually assisted in some litigation against one of that attorney’s former clients. The case was interesting because it was one of those situations I had come to appreciate: someone puts all the protections in place before the problems start, instead of scrambling to try to fix a problem at a time when they should’ve had the protections in place already.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNDERSTANDING JURISDICTION</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/understanding-jurisdiction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/understanding-jurisdiction/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In all of history there has been but one successful protest against an income tax. It is little understood in that light, primarily because the remnants of protest groups still exist, but no longer wish to appear to be &amp;ldquo;anti-government.&amp;rdquo; They don’t talk much about these roots. Few even know them. We need to go back in time about 400 years to find this success. It succeeded only because the term &amp;ldquo;jurisdiction&amp;rdquo; was still well understood at that time as meaning &amp;ldquo;oath spoken.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Juris,&amp;rdquo; in the original Latin meaning, is &amp;ldquo;oath.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Diction&amp;rdquo; as everyone knows, means &amp;ldquo;spoken.&amp;rdquo; The protest obviously didn’t happen here. It occurred in England. Given that the origins of our law are traced there, most of the relevant facts in this matter are still applicable in this nation. Here’s what happened.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trustees In Commerce: A Way of Life</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/trustees-in-commerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/trustees-in-commerce/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, take all that and place a simple barrier between the &amp;ldquo;sovereign&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;secured party&amp;rdquo; and commerce. The barrier is called an&#xA;Express Trust under the Common Law. Throw out the fragile sovereign crown andgive the man a bulletproof trustee helmet. Now, instead of him owning a plot of land with a castle, havinga royal army and a royal staff of workers, stockpiling his own weapons, having Federal Reserve Notes orminted coins in his personal possession, and understanding all applicable bodies of law to protecthimself— he now does these things on behalf of a trust. Problem solved.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attorney General Money</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/attorney-general-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/attorney-general-money/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It was mentioned by a member, that the concept of ATTORNEY GENERAL MONEY was not well known; so this is to clean up any misconceptions and to make a few things clear.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In order for any money to be useful, it must be ACCEPTED by all PARTIES. Since every country that the International Monetary Fund (IMF) touches is in receivership, any money created must comply with the IMF’s receivership rules. As with everything the U.S. dollar touches, the rules are designed to exploit the ignorant. For hundreds of years corporations have made their own money as a matter of course. What did you think “in-store credit” was? However, in order for money to be “LEGAL” it MUST have the following:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who’s On First: FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/whos-on-first-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/whos-on-first-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h5 id=&#34;whos-on-first-for-idiots-c-2015-roguesupport-inc-under-a-creative-commons-attribution-noncommercial-noderivs-30-unported-license&#34;&gt;Who’s On First: FOR IDIOTS (c) 2015 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For anyone still lagging behind in the “name game” confusion surrounding systems relating to law and money, I present, “Who’s on First?”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also for your edification, I have copied/pasted the opening sentences from Wikipedia describing the comedy routine, below:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Who’s on First?” is descended from turn-of-the-century burlesque sketches that used plays on words and names. Examples are “The Baker Scene” (the shop is located on Watt Street) and “Who Dyed” (the owner is named Who). In the 1930 movie Cracked Nuts, comedians Bert Wheeler and Robert Woolsey examine a map of a mythical kingdom with dialogue like this: “What is next to Which.” “What is the name of the town next to Which?” “Yes.” In English music halls (Britain’s equivalent of vaudeville theaters), comedian Will Hay performed a routine in the early 1930s (and possibly earlier) as a schoolmaster interviewing a schoolboy named Howe who came from Ware but now lives in Wye. By the early 1930s, a “Baseball Routine” had become a standard bit for burlesque comics across the United States. Abbott’s wife recalled Bud performing the routine with another comedian before teaming with Costello.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvel Jesus, Better Than Jesus, &amp; The Sermon on The Keyboard</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/marvel-jesus-better-than-jesus-and-the-sermon-on-the-keyboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/marvel-jesus-better-than-jesus-and-the-sermon-on-the-keyboard/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/bc2df4c5-c6d4-4394-9f85-b5deaf00356a&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;marvel-jesus-better-than-jesus--the-sermon-on-the-keyboard&#34;&gt;Marvel Jesus, Better Than Jesus, &amp;amp; The Sermon on The Keyboard&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Appointed by &amp;ldquo;N&amp;rdquo; for &amp;ldquo;Not Surety&amp;rdquo;,&#xA;A reference to THE TENDER FOR LAW on Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Shared under a Creative Commons 3.0 Unported License; BY-ND-NC&#xA;(c) INGENIUM HOLDINGS INCORPORATED&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I promised to handle this “thing” with the greatest care, so &amp;ldquo;what is it?&amp;rdquo; you might ask, how did I become a holder of it, and what does this stewardship mean? What does accounting have to do with the “Kingdom of God”?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Channeling Nancy (Or; Why Lying Is Really Bad…)</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/channeling-nancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/channeling-nancy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A Tender For Law Article by Ceit Butler(c), under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am what you would describe as “an avid reader”. I started young; my grandmother had taught me to read chapter books by the time I turned 3, and in doing so she forever instilled in me a love of reading. I spent the majority of my formative years with my nose buried in a book. I read everything that I could get my hands on; comic books, encyclopedias, scientific guides, and novels. I spent days at a time exploring other worlds, as familiar with the landscapes of Narnia, Middle Earth, Olympus, and Xanth as I was with my own backyard. Visions of the future – some glorious, others terrifying – awaited me each month in the pages of Issac Asimov’s Science Fiction Magazine. I spent my nights, hiding under my blanket with flashlight in hand, wandering the dark hallways that sprang from the imagination of Lovecraft and Poe. And last, but not least, I solved mysteries alongside the likes of Sherlock Holmes, Miss Marple, and Hercule Poirot.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Show Me The Money</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/show-me-the-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/show-me-the-money/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 id=&#34;c-ingenium-holdings-incorporated-under-a-creative-commons-30-unported-license-by-nd-nc&#34;&gt;(c) INGENIUM HOLDINGS INCORPORATED under a Creative Commons 3.0 Unported License; BY-ND-NC&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you’re like me, for most of your life you’ve had minimal conscious interactions with ACCOUNTING, It was always presented to me as something very boring and complicated so I&amp;rsquo;d always avoided learning about it. While embracing my love of ignorance &lt;strong&gt;I COULD NOT SEE&lt;/strong&gt; how this &lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACTION&lt;/strong&gt; was being used against me every day or how I could use it for my benefit.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hero&#39;s Journey</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/hero-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/hero-journey/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;every-one-lives-out-a-myth-and-you-should-know-what-your-myth-is-because-maybe-its-a-tragedy&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;Every one lives out a myth, and you should know what your myth is because maybe it&amp;rsquo;s a tragedy&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jews stole your birthright, now there’s only ritual without reflection.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hero&#39;s_journey&#34;&gt;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hero&amp;rsquo;s_journey&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The point of the Hero’s Story is to discover who One could become. One goes in[put] and comes out[put] transformed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 id=&#34;you-dont-know-who-you-are&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;You don&amp;rsquo;t know who you are&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;-Scott Duncan&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most of us don&amp;rsquo;t even start the journey, or use a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/j/journal.asp&#34;&gt;journal&lt;/a&gt;, because belief acts as a barrier that &amp;ldquo;protects&amp;rdquo; us from the unknown. Through belief we&amp;rsquo;ve damaged the mechanism that was supposed to guide us in developing our story of turning the unknown into the known; repeatedly. The mechanism is something like: “the courageous commitment to go out [look], find what&amp;rsquo;s true, and to speak it to others so they might also choose to find it&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
