<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Responsibility on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/categories/responsibility/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Responsibility on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/categories/responsibility/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Trust But Verify</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/trust-but-verify/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/trust-but-verify/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Scott always said to us: &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t know what you don&amp;rsquo;t know&amp;rdquo;. I now see how true this is. He always said too: &amp;ldquo;I can&amp;rsquo;t dumb it down any further, you have to meet me in the middle.&amp;rdquo; The 2 things are true. The reason it can&amp;rsquo;t be dumbed down any further is because of the language. The language of the Angols (English) was stolen from you and forked to legalese. It&amp;rsquo;s a bastardized form of English that doesn&amp;rsquo;t use synonyms or homonyms. Each term has 1 meaning. Anthony Massoli has posted from his notes, the most obvious of these. The one I&amp;rsquo;ve found that is most different is transportation. Alan Day is a direct descendant of the people affected by this.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Article About Accounting</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/an-article-about-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/an-article-about-accounting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I was asked to write an article on Accounting. This is a VERY BROAD topic. There are also very significant differences in performing accounting for a security in receivership or a corporation or even a trust. I try to perform all the duties that I am APPOINTED to do, but this one is quite the challenge.&#xA;So I have a better idea. Let&amp;rsquo;s have an interactive thread on strictly ACCOUNTING. Ask your questions here and I will try to show you what the answers are and how you can verify them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURETY FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/surety-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/surety-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW – SURETY FOR IDIOTS (c) 2013 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It’s been a while since I’ve posted an article, and I’ve solidified the “For Idiots” concept. Let’s cover SURETY!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the most painful things about being on FaceBook is having to endure the fact that people with chronic Dunning–Kruger effect still think that their ignorance has the same standing as my knowledge; and they will happily state many unkind things regarding my character when I challenge their “pulled-out-of-their-ass” mythology.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hero&#39;s Journey</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/hero-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/hero-journey/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;every-one-lives-out-a-myth-and-you-should-know-what-your-myth-is-because-maybe-its-a-tragedy&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;Every one lives out a myth, and you should know what your myth is because maybe it&amp;rsquo;s a tragedy&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jews stole your birthright, now there’s only ritual without reflection.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hero&#39;s_journey&#34;&gt;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hero&amp;rsquo;s_journey&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The point of the Hero’s Story is to discover who One could become. One goes in[put] and comes out[put] transformed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 id=&#34;you-dont-know-who-you-are&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;You don&amp;rsquo;t know who you are&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;-Scott Duncan&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most of us don&amp;rsquo;t even start the journey, or use a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/j/journal.asp&#34;&gt;journal&lt;/a&gt;, because belief acts as a barrier that &amp;ldquo;protects&amp;rdquo; us from the unknown. Through belief we&amp;rsquo;ve damaged the mechanism that was supposed to guide us in developing our story of turning the unknown into the known; repeatedly. The mechanism is something like: “the courageous commitment to go out [look], find what&amp;rsquo;s true, and to speak it to others so they might also choose to find it&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Prodigal Son</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/the-prodigal-son/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/the-prodigal-son/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A few words on the subject of being right.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My name is Scott Duncan.  I am trusted with a lot of secrets, and I keep those secrets by being honest.  It&amp;rsquo;s counter-intuitive, but it works profoundly well.  I write on these relatively obscure mediums which, while public, aren&amp;rsquo;t actively promoted.  This is by design.  Only those who have been following me for the past four years will truly understand what I&amp;rsquo;m saying here; and the rest of you, of course, will misinterpret it.  Know that any action that you take based on that misinterpretation, is by design.  I fully expect you to do the wrong thing, based on the wrong perception, and when you do, that makes you my servant.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Piece-of-Shit-Christians are Pieces of shit: Why Rational Discourse is Futile</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/piece-of-shit-christians-are-pieces-of-shit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/piece-of-shit-christians-are-pieces-of-shit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Did you know I&amp;rsquo;m an Ordained Minister?  It&amp;rsquo;s true.  I can legally marry people in Texas.  I&amp;rsquo;ve been to Texas twice in my life; both times I wasn&amp;rsquo;t there for more than a week.  I did, however, use my time efficiently and invested it to become an Ordained Minister of the &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;Church of the Subgenius&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; (Praise Bob!).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If you see something, say something!</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/if-you-see-something-say-something/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/if-you-see-something-say-something/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;[Originally posted on Facebook, Tuesday May 3, 2016]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Have you read Aldous Huxley&amp;rsquo;s Brave New World (1932),  George Orwell&amp;rsquo;s Animal Farm (1945) and Nineteen Eighty Four (1949) , Ray Bradbury&amp;rsquo;s Fahrenheit 451 (1953), or seen the movies,  Brazil (1985) and Idiocracy (2006)?    What about books by Douglas Adams, Isaac Asimov,  Alfred Bester,  Arthur C. Clarke,  Philip K. Dick,  William Gibson,  Frank Herbert, Robert A. Heinlein,  Larry Niven,  Jerry Pournelle,  Jules Verne, H. G. Wells?   Some of you have.   It&amp;rsquo;s likely your children have not.  We have to protect our children from independent thought,  wherever possible - or so I&amp;rsquo;m told.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bullying 2.0</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/bullying2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/bullying2.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Prologue:  I wrote this for someone, but it may otherwise have some small value.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Bullying. Now there&amp;rsquo;s a topic. As long as there have been people who were stronger, wealthier, in more &amp;ldquo;senior&amp;rdquo; positions, better armed, meaner, dumber, less emotionally stable, there has been &amp;ldquo;bullying&amp;rdquo;. It has its own term, and there is evidence of activities that fall into this category for all of recorded history.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
