<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2 on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/2/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2 on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>YOU THINK WRONG, AND VALUE THE WRONG THINGS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/you-think-wrong-and-value-the-wrong-things/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/you-think-wrong-and-value-the-wrong-things/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: YOU THINK WRONG AND VALUE THE WRONG THINGS – By Tara Duncan (c) 2015 ROGUESUPPORT INC.  under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License. While this is predominantly directed at personal friends and acquaintances, there are perhaps some FB group members who may benefit from the information in this article, as well. This should not be new information to most. It does seem, however, to be a repeating theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Our Thoughts and Prayers are With You</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/thoughts-and-prayers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/thoughts-and-prayers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;ve heard this once, you&amp;rsquo;ve heard it a hundred times. Someone is sick, in trouble, dead, struggling with some real or perceived problem&amp;hellip;you know the drill; and some well-wisher informs you that their personal, family, club, organization or social-circle&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;thoughts and prayers&amp;rdquo; are with you. You see this frequently in news articles, on social media sites, and from friends and relatives in personal conversation. You listen politely, for you are the epitome of social correctness, and thank them for their kindness. Yet, does anyone ever wonder how these thoughts and prayers might do anything for you?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOTICE OF MISTAKE</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/notice-of-mistake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/notice-of-mistake/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;(c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;notice-of-mistake--get-these-to-me-if-im-arrested&#34;&gt;NOTICE OF MISTAKE – GET THESE TO ME IF I’M ARRESTED&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;NOTICE OF MISTAKE&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;TAKE NOTICE THAT: In the matter of SURETY for the LEGAL NAME, I believe that there has been a MISTAKE, as the SOLE BENEFICIARY OF A PUBLIC DOCUMENT has been INCORRECTLY IDENTIFIED as an “accused” and/or a “suspect”.&#xA;FORGIVE ME: If I, AND/OR PERSONS AND/OR FRIENDS OF THE COURT AND/OR SUCH OTHER PARTIES ACTING IN MY INTERESTS, have led A COURT and/or STATUTORY BODY and/or A GOVERNMENT SERVICE and/or AGENTS and/or OFFICERS of such bodies, to believe, by responding to “You”, and/or “JOHN SCOTT DUNCAN”, and/or SUCH OTHER IDENTIFICATION, such bodies HAVE ADDRESSED ME AS, that I am the PARTY WITH SURETY in this matter, then that would be a MISTAKE, and please forgive me.&#xA;If I, AND/OR PERSONS AND/OR FRIENDS OF THE COURT AND/OR SUCH OTHER PARTIES ACTING IN MY INTERESTS, have led A COURT and/or STATUTORY BODY and/or A GOVERNMENT SERVICE and/or AGENTS and/or OFFICERS of such bodies, to believe, by responding to “You”, and/or “JOHN SCOTT DUNCAN”, and/or SUCH OTHER IDENTIFICATION, such bodies HAVE ADDRESSED ME AS, that I am, in ANY CAPACITY, a Pro Se litigant  and/or a LEGAL PERSON in this matter, then that would be a MISTAKE, as I DO NOT CONSENT and WAIVE THE BENEFIT to such titles (Waiver of the CHANGE OF NAMES ACT OF ONTARIO), and please forgive me.&#xA;THEREFORE: As I have no knowledge of who “You” and or “JOHN SCOTT DUNCAN” and/or SUCH OTHER IDENTIFICATION ANY COURT and/or STATUTORY BODY and/or GOVERNMENT SERVICE and/or AGENTS and/or OFFICERS of such bodies [HEREAFTER “YOU”], HAS ADDRESSED ME AS, I RESPECTFULLY ASK; by WHAT AUTHORITY ARE “YOU” ADDRESSING me as such?&#xA;As the SURETY BOND (BIRTH CERTIFICATE) has been deposited into the COURT [In the custody of Justice Wailan Low, ONTARIO SUPERIOR COURT OF JUSTICE: Court File Number CV-11-430464], WHAT EVIDENCE does the COURT have that I, as a MAN who is not lawfully entitled to the BENEFITS of a BIRTH CERTIFICATE [PPSACA13078], have any SURETY in this matter?&#xA;As GOVERNMENT is the SOLE SIGNATORY PARTY on the SURETY BOND (BIRTH CERTIFICATE), with SOLE AND FULL SURETY as TRUSTEE for the LEGAL NAME, WHAT EVIDENCE do YOU have that I am a TRUSTEE for the LEGAL NAME. WHAT EVIDENCE do YOU have that I am a TRUSTEE and have ANY SURETY with respect to ANY NAME?&#xA;WHAT EVIDENCE do YOU have, that I am an OFFICER, an AGENT, a TRUSTEE and/or an EMPLOYEE of the CROWN? WHAT EVIDENCE do “YOU” have of any WARRANT OF AGENCY for the principal?&#xA;WHAT EVIDENCE do “YOU” have that there has been any meeting of the minds, any PROPER NOTICE given, any considerable CONSIDERATION offered, or that I have ANY INTENT to CONTRACT in this matter?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attorney General Money</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/attorney-general-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/attorney-general-money/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It was mentioned by a member, that the concept of ATTORNEY GENERAL MONEY was not well known; so this is to clean up any misconceptions and to make a few things clear.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In order for any money to be useful, it must be ACCEPTED by all PARTIES. Since every country that the International Monetary Fund (IMF) touches is in receivership, any money created must comply with the IMF’s receivership rules. As with everything the U.S. dollar touches, the rules are designed to exploit the ignorant. For hundreds of years corporations have made their own money as a matter of course. What did you think “in-store credit” was? However, in order for money to be “LEGAL” it MUST have the following:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JOINDER FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/joinder-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/joinder-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: JOINDER FOR IDIOTS (c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Well, spring is here.  The days are getting longer, tulips and other spring shit are showing up; I’m sure somewhere there are robins and stuff, and the FREE-DUMBERS seem to have bred and left shit-stains all over.  It’s time to do something about that.Today we are going to discuss the LEGAL NAME, the different case and spelling, and what it REALLY means.Your average FREE-DUMBER will say your capitalized name is a “CORPORATION”, and will attempt to sound smart by saying Latin phrases like, “Capitus Dickus Erectus“, or some other such nonsense that has no bearing on reality.  The case and spelling of your name is the direct result of administrative policy – and nothing more.  As many of you former fuck-wits have learned, none of this is hidden.  They must give NOTICE, so they can make their presumptions, because “ignorance of the law is no excuse”.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEGALESE FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/legalese-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/legalese-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;legalese-for-idiots&#34;&gt;LEGALESE FOR IDIOTS&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW – LEGALESE FOR IDIOTS (c) 2013 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It’s feast or famine around here at THE TENDER FOR LAW. This is article number two in as many days!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Derek Moran says that he finds it difficult to believe that I will be able to top the SURETY article…CHALLENGE ACCEPTED.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is almost midnight on Sunday, I’m on the bridge of the Tycho-Brahe, and as I look out onto the lake the water is like a sheet of glass…and it’s not even frozen. How can I not produce a superior article tonight? So today, with all my “God” complex, “arrogance”, and the knowledge that a host of “pseudo radio” is reading my superior work, and knowing that all he can do is tremble in impotent fury. Things are so good I can cover the bad aspects of law, namely its language.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INSURANCE FOR THE INEPT</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/insurance-for-the-inept/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/insurance-for-the-inept/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW – APPOINTED ARTICLE – INSURANCE FOR THE INEPT – By APPOINTMENT of Gail Blackman (c) 2013 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the great things about being in a law forum, run by a prorogued noble, is that you have the unique opportunity of posing the right question and always getting a near-magical answer; which causes something to flip in that little lump of protoplasm you laughingly call a brain.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIES AND THE LYING LIARS WHO LIE ABOUT THE LIES THEY TELL</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/lies-and-lying-liars-who-lie-about-the-liaes-they-tell/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/lies-and-lying-liars-who-lie-about-the-liaes-they-tell/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;lies-and-the-lying-liars-who-lie-about-the-lies-they-tell-an-objective-and-fair-analysis-of-the-law-society&#34;&gt;LIES AND THE LYING LIARS WHO LIE ABOUT THE LIES THEY TELL: An Objective and Fair Analysis of the LAW SOCIETY&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: LIES AND THE LYING LIARS WHO LIE ABOUT THE LIES THEY TELL: An Objective and Fair Analysis of the LAW SOCIETY (c) 2016 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As of this writing the Roguesupport Initiative, THE TENDER FOR LAW, is 3.75 years old. The project was started on FaceBook for numerous reasons, one of which was that it meets the LEGAL burden of “PUBLIC RECORD”. In theory, what I write on Facebook could be read by over one billion people. Here in reality, that’s not very likely, but it’s also not very likely that you ever went to the classified ads in the newspaper intentionally looking for “LEGAL NOTICES”, either. It doesn’t matter if people read the notice, it simply has to be “made available” in a manner that one could reasonably access. It’s not difficult to go to your public library and look up the contents of an old newspaper. It’s even easier to obtain a Facebook account. The “LEGAL BURDEN” has been met.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obiter Dictum: MEADS V. MEADS FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/obiter-dictum-meades-v-meads-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/obiter-dictum-meades-v-meads-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;obiter-dictum-meads-v-meads-for-idiots&#34;&gt;Obiter Dictum: MEADS V. MEADS FOR IDIOTS&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: Obiter dictum: MEADS v. MEADS FOR IDIOTS (c) 2015 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It’s time to stir the pot – disturb some shit as it were, stoke the fire, prime the forge, enrich uranium in a centrifuge, shit like that. In order to accomplish this noble goal I’m going to do something that, on the surface, seems disgusting. I’m going to arm the FREE-DUMBERS WITH THE KNOWLEDGE TO CRUSH MEADS V. MEADS. If you’re really lucky, I’ll try to squeeze in some “Nazis” too. If this seems a little “rushed, it’s because this was published BY APPOINTMENT!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THERE ARE NO GIRLS ON THE INTERNET</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/no-girls-on-the-interent/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/no-girls-on-the-interent/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;THERE ARE NO GIRLS ON THE INTERNET&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before we get to the post, a little history; Half of this will sound familiar because it&amp;rsquo;s an Internet meme! You can look it up!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;@TaraDuncan knows herself, with absolute certainty, that the history on the public record is made-up bullshit, because She took dictation when the first half was done. That&amp;rsquo;s right, it was stripped of its point/counterpoint context, and only my half was posted&amp;hellip;years after this.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Irish Rocco</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/irish-rocco/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/irish-rocco/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;irish-rocco&#34;&gt;IRISH ROCCO!&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So @DaveCullen plays the naive &amp;ldquo;useful idiot&amp;rsquo; and sets you all up for a fleecing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.minds.com/newsfeed/1141794890200764416&#34;&gt;https://www.minds.com/newsfeed/1141794890200764416&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How? Well let&amp;rsquo;s walk through it, shall we?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m going to sound like a broken record here, but you don&amp;rsquo;t actually listen to the axioms you affectionately call &amp;ldquo;Scottisms&amp;rdquo;. You&amp;rsquo;ll hear the words, and you&amp;rsquo;ll comprehend their meaning. Like many of the things I tell you, when you hear them you know they&amp;rsquo;re true. When reminded, you&amp;rsquo;ll nod sagely in the knowledge you have this useful information. Time will pass, and you&amp;rsquo;ll need to be reminded again.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Somebody Called Me A Cunt</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/somebody-called-me-a-cunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/somebody-called-me-a-cunt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Somebody called me a &amp;ldquo;cunt&amp;rdquo; once on social media. Actually to be fair more than a few people have called me this or something similar at intervals over the years; sometimes variations on this theme with greater or fewer adjectives, perhaps according to their whims, creative abilities or the occasion. This seemed dependent on their perception of how much I had offended their delicate sensibilities by simply disagreeing with whatever idea or belief they held.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We Get Phone Calls</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/we-get-phone-calls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/we-get-phone-calls/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Do you ever get those phone calls from Asian-sounding gentlemen offering assistance because your &amp;ldquo;Windows PC&amp;rdquo; is infected? They have, they say, discovered some vulnerability through their advanced internet scanning software. These kindly strangers can help you secure your machine. Some of you with more advanced computer skills (and perhaps a Windows virtual machine) may engage these people in hours of unforgettable merriment. However most of you should just hang up the phone; in the &amp;ldquo;big-shock&amp;rdquo; department this process involves giving access to your computer software, being locked out of the machine, and then &amp;ldquo;buying&amp;rdquo; the user/password information back. In short this is a malicious money-making scam. As quick cash grabs go though, it could be worse. There is an endless supply of people and organizations that exist to capitalize on the credulity of the ignorant.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Politeness vs. Political Correctness</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/politeness-vs-polticalcorrectness/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/politeness-vs-polticalcorrectness/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[Language and concepts contained herein may offend some with delicate constitutions.  If you are one of these people, please immediately stop reading]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;A dying culture invariably exhibits personal rudeness. Bad manners. Lack of consideration for others in minor matters. A loss of politeness, of gentle manners, is more significant than is a riot.” - Robert A. Heinlein, Friday&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While out with a friend, I watched as she held a door open for a passing pedestrian.  She had actually opened the door for herself, but stood back to allow an approaching man to enter the building first.  My friend is nothing if not polite.  The man, his interest firmly focused on the contents of his wireless device, sailed through the door without even looking up.  We then waited as a parade of other strangers drafted wireless guy through the door, laughing and talking amongst themselves.  Not one of them even acknowledged my friend in her new role as unpaid door person.  When the way was finally clear, my friend and I exchanged glances and moved on.  We have been having this &amp;ldquo;glance exchange&amp;rdquo; more frequently over the last few years in response to a growing number of minor, but oddly significant lapses in social etiquette exhibited by the general public.  Common courtesy is becoming uncommon.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just Do It</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/just-do-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2016 03:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/just-do-it/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I recently read an article which purports to tell you six harsh truths about yourself. It appeared to supply one &amp;ldquo;truth&amp;rdquo; in six parts, but it&amp;rsquo;s a reasonable one at least. Loosely paraphrased, it says that people who want to do something, do it. The things in question should be considered achievable, in case you&amp;rsquo;re mounting a counterpoint. So if you&amp;rsquo;re not doing that thing you love, anything else is just rhetoric.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DEFAMATORY LIBEL FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/defamatory-libel-for-odiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/defamatory-libel-for-odiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-tender-for-law-defamatory-libel-for-idiots-a-serendipitously-happily-coincidental-article-c-1982-2015-roguesupport-inc-under-a-creative-commons-attribution-noncommercial-noderivs-30-unported-license&#34;&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: DEFAMATORY LIBEL FOR IDIOTS; A Serendipitously, Happily-Coincidental Article (c) 1982-2015 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In case none of you read that LICENSE, that means that no COMMERCE is expected and/or IMPLIED…again, in case you are confused.  Only members of THE TENDER FOR LAW will understand why that’s so important.  ALSO: there are no “answers” here, just a “setting of the scene” as it were…&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CORPUS DELICTI</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/corpus-dilecti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/corpus-dilecti/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:1313/img/murder.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;CORPUS DELICTI&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: PERSONS FOR IDIOTS (c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“CORPUS DELICTI” The MOST IGNORED LEGAL CONCEPT!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The circle-jerkers at Quatloos have been scouring the 1960 CANADIAN BILL OF RIGHTS for what is supposedly my own “crazy” position that for a CRIME, there must be an INJURED PARTY. They LOVE cherry-picking, or just plain ignoring the maxim of CORPUS DELICTI! Even their precious “Justices” agree with me!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Give In Lieu Of “Identification”</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/given-in-leiu-of-identification/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/given-in-leiu-of-identification/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;give-in-lieu-of-identification&#34;&gt;Give In Lieu Of “Identification”&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;NOTICE OF WAIVER OF PUBLIC BENEFITS (ONTARIO CHANGE OF NAME ACT  [R.S.O. 1990, CHAPTER C.7])&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;WHEREAS YOU, being a PUBLIC SERVANT and/or an OFFICER for a PUBLIC TRUST, and/or A GOVERNMENT AGENT/OFFICIAL, have demanded “IDENTIFICATION” from ME, and&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;WHEREAS YOU, being a PUBLIC SERVANT and/or an OFFICER for a PUBLIC TRUST, and/or A GOVERNMENT AGENT/OFFICIAL, do NOT have the right, and/or AUTHORITY, to attach SURETY and/or JOINDER, to ANY NAME DERIVED FROM A PUBLIC DOCUMENT, and attach such NAME and/or JOINDER to ME, and&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IT’S ALL NATURAL!</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/its-all-natural/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/its-all-natural/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;26 June 2014 at 20:40&#xA;You often hear me lament the fact that there are people who only pretend to think.  I often counter this unfortunate phenomenon with Tim Minchin’s “Storm”.   More specifically, I reference the quote “Do you know what they call alternative medicine that’s been proven to work?  …medicine”.   The alternative medicine crowd has no idea what this means, as they consider PhotoShop pictures and Youtube videos “proof”.  They try to look “sciency”, but rarely have anything resembling proof, while always seeming to have a “store”.  This, in and of itself, should make you suspicious about the self-serving nature of anything being recommended, but the larger issue is with the process itself.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Libertarians and My Cat</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/libertarians-and-my-cat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/libertarians-and-my-cat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;libertarians-and-my-cat&#34;&gt;Libertarians And My Cat&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: Libertarians and my cat. (c) 2015  ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Figure 1: This is Meko and Trouble. They are cats&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Figure 2: This is Larken Rose. He is a Libertarian. He recently said:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“There are plenty of different legalese mythology theories which amount to, “You accidentally and secretly AGREED and CONSENTED to be ruled by government by…” Then they end the statement with “calling yourself a ‘citizen&amp;rsquo;” or “using FRN’s” or “having a Social Security Number” or “using a bank account” or “spelling your name in all capital letters” or they say it’s about living here without filing some magic piece of paper or “declaring” something or other.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Belief Is My Conviction</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/my-belief-is-my-conviction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/my-belief-is-my-conviction/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: “MY BELIEF, IS MY CONVICTION”&#xA;(c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&#xA;I was talking to the man who once fleetingly served as helmsman of the Tycho-Brahe (known to the world as “The Fender”), heady from his pseudo-victory of seeing a legal connection that I didn’t. He decided to take a run at my ultimate CONVICTION; ALL belief is EVIL.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I’ll continue with my story, but first I want to point out (as usual) how ignorant you are. I know that really hurts your feelings, but it doesn’t make it any less true. I will not continue my story until I convince you of this fact (you ignorant fuck!).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oh Say Can&#39;t You See?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/a-primer-on-citizenship/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/a-primer-on-citizenship/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;oh-say-cant-you-see--a-primer-on-citizenship&#34;&gt;OH, SAY CAN’T YOU SEE? – A Primer On Citizenship&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: “OH, SAY CAN’T YOU SEE? – A Primer on Citizenship” (c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&#xA;In one of our many lively discussions, on the many lively forums that my captains and I chat in and/or frequent, the erstwhile Captain Wentz revealed a small but interesting factoid that surprised a few people;  He pointed out that from 1992 to 2002, he was in fact, the Admiral of the AQUILAE Navy.  I spent most of those years as a specialist and/or non-commissioned officer.  That’s right, for a while I was “Scotty” in the engine room.  The reason I’m not doing it today (despite how much I enjoyed it), is that I don’t think I could endure everyone who meets me, making a “Scotty in the engine room joke”, followed by a strange smug demeanour, like he/she was the first one to ever come up with a “Scotty in the fucking Engine Room” joke.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OMNIJURISDICTIONAL NOTICE</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/omnijurisdictional-notice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/omnijurisdictional-notice/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;omnijurisdictional-notice&#34;&gt;OMNIJURISDICTIONAL NOTICE&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: AN OMNIJURISDICTIONAL NOTICE (c) 1982-2015 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;NOTICE: This document will KEEP GROWING. CONTENT ADDED DAILY TO THIS NOTE!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ATTENTION, SIMU-DRONES:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It’s 2015. Things are getting darker, but you are getting smarter. You see now, or at least grasp, how to gain wealth and power, but you are at a loss as to what to do with it if you succeed. I have GREAT news! Now you have an answer! WAR!  LET’S PRACTICE!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONE TRILLION DOLLARS!</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/one-trillion-dollars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/one-trillion-dollars/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;one-trillion-dollars&#34;&gt;ONE TRILLION DOLLARS!&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(c) 2016 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jan 28th 2016:  Scott Duncan shared Jamie Redman‘s post&#xA;HEY! Andrew D’Spyder-Pig! Looks like those evil Bitcoin folk have “thefted” a trillion bucks! 😀&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Imagine that. The awesome Satoshi Nakamoto has engineered something that “Stole” a trillion dollars, and proved the viability of the Blockchain. The entire future has been re-written, and the technologies that sprung from it, are here to stay.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Putting It All Together</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/putting-it-all-together/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/putting-it-all-together/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(c) 2013 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In THE TENDER FOR LAW&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;one of its evolved Maxims is that “The gold is in the comments”. This is true for me too, as it allows me to gauge just how much you are assimilating. Every once in a while though, a “gold nugget” comes up for me. This is no easy task, and the scarcity of this gold makes it far more valuable to me than it is to you. The question I reference came up unexpectedly and related to an incredulous observation regarding the product of my three years’ of giving actual answers and actual solutions, and telling the actual truth (all of which can be verified by the passage of time). This erstwhile interrogator asked, “Why aren’t millions of people here?”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE TENDER FOR LAW – CHILDREN’S AID SOCIETY [C.A.S] FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/childrens-aid-society-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/childrens-aid-society-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;(c) 2013 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article is what we like to call an “emergency article” in as much as Dean Clifford has publicly and blatantly lied about family services and the law. Before we get started we are going to refer to the JURISDICTION I am most familiar with. You will find mirrors of this in any JURISDICTION that uses a world reserve currency.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FREE-DUMB – THE TRUTH &amp; ROBERT MENARD</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/freedumb-the-truth-and-robert-menard/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/freedumb-the-truth-and-robert-menard/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW – Pseudo-article-to-tide-you-over-while-we-continue-work on-the-next-article:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;…OK, not really. Roll the copyright and licence!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;( Shut up! It’s coming! )&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the super-secret group, THE TENDER FOR LAW (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.facebook.com/groups/tenderforlaw/)&#34;&gt;https://www.facebook.com/groups/tenderforlaw/)&lt;/a&gt;, I was asked a very interesting question regarding how soon one of my “predictions” will come to pass.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Those that have come to know me recently, and/or those who have known me for a longer period (20 years or more), can all agree on one thing; I see shit coming, and I understand substantially more than everyone else.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONE PEOPLE’S PUBLIC FRAUD (OPPF) Part ONE</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/oppf-p1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/oppf-p1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ORIGINALLY PUBLISHED on 23 February 2013 · in THE TENDER FOR LAW:ONE PEOPLE’S PUBLIC FRAUD (OPPF) Part ONE (c) 2013 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ONE PEOPLE’S PUBLIC FRAUD (OPPF) …You’ll notice I didn’t use the word TRUST.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Scams like this diminish the word in much the same way GOVERNMENTS have diminished the words “human rights”.  As this is my forum, I think I will prevent the concept of TRUSTS being diminished any further by this scam.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
