<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Man =/= Person on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/categories/man-/-person/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Man =/= Person on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/categories/man-/-person/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Trust But Verify</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/trust-but-verify/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/trust-but-verify/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Scott always said to us: &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t know what you don&amp;rsquo;t know&amp;rdquo;. I now see how true this is. He always said too: &amp;ldquo;I can&amp;rsquo;t dumb it down any further, you have to meet me in the middle.&amp;rdquo; The 2 things are true. The reason it can&amp;rsquo;t be dumbed down any further is because of the language. The language of the Angols (English) was stolen from you and forked to legalese. It&amp;rsquo;s a bastardized form of English that doesn&amp;rsquo;t use synonyms or homonyms. Each term has 1 meaning. Anthony Massoli has posted from his notes, the most obvious of these. The one I&amp;rsquo;ve found that is most different is transportation. Alan Day is a direct descendant of the people affected by this.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PERSONS FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/persons-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/persons-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: PERSONS FOR IDIOTS (c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All of you reading have, at one point or another, encountered the term “PERSON”.  After very little investigation, you are forced to accept the realization that you are not a PERSON, rather you HAVE a PERSON. This distinction is the first “lie of ommission” that you will encounter in the world of the “LEGAL”. THE TENDER FOR LAW axiom “LEGAL=SURETY AND ACCOUNTING” makes navigating “law” a lot simpler, and it’s very easy to spot the lies of ommission/ambiguity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
