<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>#TrustButVerify on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/%23trustbutverify/</link>
    <description>Recent content in #TrustButVerify on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/%23trustbutverify/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Trust But Verify</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/trust-but-verify/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/trust-but-verify/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Scott always said to us: &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t know what you don&amp;rsquo;t know&amp;rdquo;. I now see how true this is. He always said too: &amp;ldquo;I can&amp;rsquo;t dumb it down any further, you have to meet me in the middle.&amp;rdquo; The 2 things are true. The reason it can&amp;rsquo;t be dumbed down any further is because of the language. The language of the Angols (English) was stolen from you and forked to legalese. It&amp;rsquo;s a bastardized form of English that doesn&amp;rsquo;t use synonyms or homonyms. Each term has 1 meaning. Anthony Massoli has posted from his notes, the most obvious of these. The one I&amp;rsquo;ve found that is most different is transportation. Alan Day is a direct descendant of the people affected by this.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Robbing a bank&#39;</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/robbing-a-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/robbing-a-bank/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ok, since there are no questions on the board, I guess everyone is on the same page here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lets discuss robbing a bank. 😀&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This post is appointed by Neens Jean. She thinks wrong and values the wrong things, but she really means to appoint this article.&#xA;You found some stranger on the internet who calls you a worthless sack of shit, but you read and what he says makes sense. How can the two points be right? Is he wrong? Well, lets find out. You are all &amp;ldquo;employees&amp;rdquo; who earn a living using this legal status. This means that you are using a security in receivership to, presumably, earn income. This is a worthless legal status because you will never gain. The administrators of the receivership will surely limit how well you do and make sure they do much better off of the deal of you working. So you are worthless. How do we steal back?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Piece-of-Shit-Christians are Pieces of shit: Why Rational Discourse is Futile</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/piece-of-shit-christians-are-pieces-of-shit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/piece-of-shit-christians-are-pieces-of-shit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Did you know I&amp;rsquo;m an Ordained Minister?  It&amp;rsquo;s true.  I can legally marry people in Texas.  I&amp;rsquo;ve been to Texas twice in my life; both times I wasn&amp;rsquo;t there for more than a week.  I did, however, use my time efficiently and invested it to become an Ordained Minister of the &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;Church of the Subgenius&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; (Praise Bob!).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bullying 2.0</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/bullying2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/tara-duncan/bullying2.0/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Prologue:  I wrote this for someone, but it may otherwise have some small value.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Bullying. Now there&amp;rsquo;s a topic. As long as there have been people who were stronger, wealthier, in more &amp;ldquo;senior&amp;rdquo; positions, better armed, meaner, dumber, less emotionally stable, there has been &amp;ldquo;bullying&amp;rdquo;. It has its own term, and there is evidence of activities that fall into this category for all of recorded history.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
