<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>#TitleAndTrust on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/%23titleandtrust/</link>
    <description>Recent content in #TitleAndTrust on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/%23titleandtrust/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Those Who Mistrust</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/those-who-mis-trust/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/those-who-mis-trust/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The title of this paper is a little tricky. We’ll just clarify at the outset that those who mistrust— miss trusts. Those who mistrust are those who make a serious mistake. What I will be discussing is the mistake of missing the point about Express Trusts and the advantages of using Express Trusts wisely.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To illustrate I will tell you about a peculiar case I worked on in 2002 with an attorney who contacted me on a recommendation from the attorney who I actually assisted in some litigation against one of that attorney’s former clients. The case was interesting because it was one of those situations I had come to appreciate: someone puts all the protections in place before the problems start, instead of scrambling to try to fix a problem at a time when they should’ve had the protections in place already.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trustees In Commerce: A Way of Life</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/trustees-in-commerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/trustees-in-commerce/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, take all that and place a simple barrier between the &amp;ldquo;sovereign&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;secured party&amp;rdquo; and commerce. The barrier is called an&#xA;Express Trust under the Common Law. Throw out the fragile sovereign crown andgive the man a bulletproof trustee helmet. Now, instead of him owning a plot of land with a castle, havinga royal army and a royal staff of workers, stockpiling his own weapons, having Federal Reserve Notes orminted coins in his personal possession, and understanding all applicable bodies of law to protecthimself— he now does these things on behalf of a trust. Problem solved.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Article About Accounting</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/an-article-about-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/an-article-about-accounting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I was asked to write an article on Accounting. This is a VERY BROAD topic. There are also very significant differences in performing accounting for a security in receivership or a corporation or even a trust. I try to perform all the duties that I am APPOINTED to do, but this one is quite the challenge.&#xA;So I have a better idea. Let&amp;rsquo;s have an interactive thread on strictly ACCOUNTING. Ask your questions here and I will try to show you what the answers are and how you can verify them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Robbing a bank&#39;</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/robbing-a-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/robbing-a-bank/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ok, since there are no questions on the board, I guess everyone is on the same page here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lets discuss robbing a bank. 😀&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This post is appointed by Neens Jean. She thinks wrong and values the wrong things, but she really means to appoint this article.&#xA;You found some stranger on the internet who calls you a worthless sack of shit, but you read and what he says makes sense. How can the two points be right? Is he wrong? Well, lets find out. You are all &amp;ldquo;employees&amp;rdquo; who earn a living using this legal status. This means that you are using a security in receivership to, presumably, earn income. This is a worthless legal status because you will never gain. The administrators of the receivership will surely limit how well you do and make sure they do much better off of the deal of you working. So you are worthless. How do we steal back?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE TENDER FOR LAW: The Looming Threat Of FreeDumb</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/the-looming-threat-of-freedumb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/the-looming-threat-of-freedumb/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Looming Threat of FreeDumb (c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this writing I shall go further into my Noble Title, the Trust I commissioned in 1982, the Constitution, and the term ‘Freeman’.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My grandfather (John Clark Duncan) was an extraordinary man.  He was of Noble descent, and served the Royal House of Windsor in World War II, training fighter pilots and later joining the 435/436 Burma Star Squadron; where he was remembered for saving a bunch of people’s asses  (and giving somebody else the credit), and depth-charging a whale off the coast of Vancouver island.Most people are unaware of the events of 1933 and the Treaty of Westminster, a long dry, boring, convoluted document that released the subjects of the Monarchy, demoted Nobles to the status of Subject, and made all of their descendants, and current “Subjects”, Freemen.  The remaining bills granting that status were signed by John Diefenbaker in 1960, and here’s where the legal shell game begins.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE TENDER FOR LAW: The Looming Threat Of FreeDumb – ADDENDUM</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/the-looming-threat-of-freedumb-addendum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/the-looming-threat-of-freedumb-addendum/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: The Looming Threat of FreeDumb – ADDENDUM (c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License. ADDENDUM TO [ https://www.facebook.com/notes/scott-duncan/the-tender-for-law-the-looming-threat-of-freedumb/815869621812845 ]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I received a message from a woman today that filled me with both anger and despair.  As you may have guessed, I justifiably hold all of you in the highest contempt.  Often I find myself longing for the mindset and ethical structure (or lack thereof) that would allow me to take my many extraordinary abilities, and just kill you all.  I won’t lie to you…it’s not for your safety, it’s for mine.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONE PEOPLE’S PUBLIC FRAUD (OPPF) Part TWO: The UCC For Idiots</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/oppf-p2-ucc-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/oppf-p2-ucc-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;one-peoples-public-fraud-oppf-part-two-the-ucc-for-idiots&#34;&gt;ONE PEOPLE’S PUBLIC FRAUD (OPPF) Part TWO: The UCC For Idiots&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ORIGINALLY PUBLISHED on 24 February 2013 · in THE TENDER FOR LAW: ONE PEOPLE’S PUBLIC FRAUD (OPPF) Part TWO: The UCC for Idiots (c) 2013 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&#xA;As promised, I am now going to cover the UNIFORM COMMERCIAL CODE (or UCC, for you idiots who type with your thumbs.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;FUCK! Myths about THIS shit, sure has “done the rounds”, hasn’t it? No more myths have been generated, out of a piece of regulation, than the UNIFORM COMMERCIAL CODE!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
