<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>#ItsTheJews on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/%23itsthejews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in #ItsTheJews on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/%23itsthejews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Who Does The World Owe 53 Trillion Dollars To?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/who-does-the-world-owe-53-trillion-dollars-to/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/who-does-the-world-owe-53-trillion-dollars-to/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A friend asked me to write something about this, so I figured what better place to write about taxation than in this group.&#xA;What is taxation? If you use the property, isn&amp;rsquo;t it fair to pay for the usage? How can this be theft? I hope to answer these questions in the body here and in the comments if necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, you have to understand that when your parents filled out an application for a Birth Certificate, the government has to reorganize itself to account for a new organization on its books. The government has both a liability to the organization and the organization has duties owed to the government. The government borrows against the future duties in order to fulfill its obligations. Wait, what did I just say? It borrows against the future of an organization to fulfill its&amp;rsquo; duties to the organization. Yes, it saddles the organization with debt to fulfill its debt. Currently, the National Debt of the United States is almost $20 trillion. (Which shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a thing here in reality, but it is) The government is borrowing using private banks as brokers against this organizations&amp;rsquo; future which represents you. It shouldn&amp;rsquo;t take a mathematician to see the fraudulent nature of this. Of course if there was disclosure, there would be no fraud, but did any of you ever get disclosure on this? I didn&amp;rsquo;t think so&amp;hellip;..anyway&amp;hellip;.. Because there is debt in transit, which is money, a security must be issued. This security is a Bill of Lading. While the cargo is in your possession, you are liable for it. The cargo is debt. (Unfortunately, I can&amp;rsquo;t think of a simpler way to communicate this)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m Not Authorized To Answer Questions</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/im-not-authorized-to-answer-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/im-not-authorized-to-answer-questions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You will need this soon, and it may save your life, so PAY ATTENTION.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;IF YOU ARE ARRESTED: You DO NOT TALK TO POLICE, and NEVER ANSWER QUESTIONS. If they say &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rsquo;re under arrest&amp;rdquo;, you don&amp;rsquo;t answer ANY question. Even if it sounds &amp;ldquo;innocent&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Police give NOTICE: In United States they say &amp;ldquo;You are under arrest for &lt;em&gt;Insert made-up bullshit here&lt;/em&gt;. You have the right to remain silent, and ANYTHING you say may (That means &amp;ldquo;will&amp;rdquo;) be used AGAINST YOU (Notice not HELP you) in a court of law. You have the right to an attorney&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; followed by bullshit you should ignore. DO NOT let ANYONE act on your behalf.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Prodigal Son</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/the-prodigal-son/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/the-prodigal-son/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A few words on the subject of being right.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My name is Scott Duncan.  I am trusted with a lot of secrets, and I keep those secrets by being honest.  It&amp;rsquo;s counter-intuitive, but it works profoundly well.  I write on these relatively obscure mediums which, while public, aren&amp;rsquo;t actively promoted.  This is by design.  Only those who have been following me for the past four years will truly understand what I&amp;rsquo;m saying here; and the rest of you, of course, will misinterpret it.  Know that any action that you take based on that misinterpretation, is by design.  I fully expect you to do the wrong thing, based on the wrong perception, and when you do, that makes you my servant.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hate Speech</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/hate-speech/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/hate-speech/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The title of this article is not just a title, it&amp;rsquo;s intent.  By intent, I mean that I intend to make this article qualify as &amp;ldquo;hate speech&amp;rdquo; according to every Western Law on the books.  That&amp;rsquo;s right, I intend to commit the &amp;ldquo;crime&amp;rdquo; of &amp;ldquo;hate speech&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Hate speech&amp;rdquo; is one of the invented crimes of the 1970&amp;rsquo;s.  It is one of the many LEGAL mechanisms used to suspend your critical thought.  Legally, &amp;ldquo;hate speech&amp;rdquo; is defined, but &amp;ldquo;hate&amp;rdquo; itself is not legally defined.  There&amp;rsquo;s a reason for this.  If &amp;ldquo;hate&amp;rdquo; were legally defined, even the most dull-witted reader would realize that any legislation that bore this definition, would literally be criminalizing an emotion.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paperwork Terroism!</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/paperwork-terrorism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/paperwork-terrorism/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t know if any of you have read this bill, C-16, and the terrifying ramifications contained therein; but if you haven&amp;rsquo;t you really should, even if you&amp;rsquo;re not in Canada.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As this &amp;ldquo;law&amp;rdquo; is currently framed, my satirical recreation of a &amp;ldquo;Gender Fluid&amp;rdquo; PSA would be a crime in Canada, for which I could be jailed.  If you think I&amp;rsquo;m being alarmist, I remind you that people have been sentenced to multiple years in prison, simply for publishing the INTENT to publish, a book questioning the Holocaust.  This happens in Germany right now.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
