<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bean Counting on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/categories/bean-counting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bean Counting on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/categories/bean-counting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>As Dumbed Down as I Can Make It</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/as-dumbed-down-as-i-can-make-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/as-dumbed-down-as-i-can-make-it/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This isn&amp;rsquo;t easy to write because you are all begging me to come down to your level. Well, I am not at your level. I have never been an &amp;ldquo;employee&amp;rdquo;, well, as an adult, and I&amp;rsquo;ve never not had tens of thousands in Accounts Receivable in case I got into a jam. I am trying really hard to dumb it down and it&amp;rsquo;s proving to be not an easy task. You are going to have to meet me halfway. &amp;hellip;.I digress&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Be a Plumber</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/how-to-be-a-plumber/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/how-to-be-a-plumber/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;By: Chris Schulte&#xA;CC BY-ND-NC 3.0 UNPORTED LICENSE&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How to be a plumber, appointed by Ricky South&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Step one is to actually know what the fuck you are doing. There is schooling involved, trade hours, etc. [someone remind me to get back to the schooling part later please]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Step 2-4: boring plumber shit.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Step 5: what to do with the ACCOUNTING!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you work 5 days a week at $90 an hour, this should bring you in about $150k per year in labor, then maybe a little more if you mark up parts. There are expenses tied to this REVENUE that can be legally accounted against this to determine INCOME. But there&amp;rsquo;s a tax on this shit, so legally, you would want INCOME to be the lowest it could be while having enough to cover personal expenses, etc. so what options do you have?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
