<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Schulte on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chris Schulte on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Who Does The World Owe 53 Trillion Dollars To?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/who-does-the-world-owe-53-trillion-dollars-to/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/who-does-the-world-owe-53-trillion-dollars-to/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A friend asked me to write something about this, so I figured what better place to write about taxation than in this group.&#xA;What is taxation? If you use the property, isn&amp;rsquo;t it fair to pay for the usage? How can this be theft? I hope to answer these questions in the body here and in the comments if necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;First, you have to understand that when your parents filled out an application for a Birth Certificate, the government has to reorganize itself to account for a new organization on its books. The government has both a liability to the organization and the organization has duties owed to the government. The government borrows against the future duties in order to fulfill its obligations. Wait, what did I just say? It borrows against the future of an organization to fulfill its&amp;rsquo; duties to the organization. Yes, it saddles the organization with debt to fulfill its debt. Currently, the National Debt of the United States is almost $20 trillion. (Which shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a thing here in reality, but it is) The government is borrowing using private banks as brokers against this organizations&amp;rsquo; future which represents you. It shouldn&amp;rsquo;t take a mathematician to see the fraudulent nature of this. Of course if there was disclosure, there would be no fraud, but did any of you ever get disclosure on this? I didn&amp;rsquo;t think so&amp;hellip;..anyway&amp;hellip;.. Because there is debt in transit, which is money, a security must be issued. This security is a Bill of Lading. While the cargo is in your possession, you are liable for it. The cargo is debt. (Unfortunately, I can&amp;rsquo;t think of a simpler way to communicate this)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trust But Verify</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/trust-but-verify/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/trust-but-verify/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Scott always said to us: &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t know what you don&amp;rsquo;t know&amp;rdquo;. I now see how true this is. He always said too: &amp;ldquo;I can&amp;rsquo;t dumb it down any further, you have to meet me in the middle.&amp;rdquo; The 2 things are true. The reason it can&amp;rsquo;t be dumbed down any further is because of the language. The language of the Angols (English) was stolen from you and forked to legalese. It&amp;rsquo;s a bastardized form of English that doesn&amp;rsquo;t use synonyms or homonyms. Each term has 1 meaning. Anthony Massoli has posted from his notes, the most obvious of these. The one I&amp;rsquo;ve found that is most different is transportation. Alan Day is a direct descendant of the people affected by this.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>As Dumbed Down as I Can Make It</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/as-dumbed-down-as-i-can-make-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/as-dumbed-down-as-i-can-make-it/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This isn&amp;rsquo;t easy to write because you are all begging me to come down to your level. Well, I am not at your level. I have never been an &amp;ldquo;employee&amp;rdquo;, well, as an adult, and I&amp;rsquo;ve never not had tens of thousands in Accounts Receivable in case I got into a jam. I am trying really hard to dumb it down and it&amp;rsquo;s proving to be not an easy task. You are going to have to meet me halfway. &amp;hellip;.I digress&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>An Article About Accounting</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/an-article-about-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/an-article-about-accounting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I was asked to write an article on Accounting. This is a VERY BROAD topic. There are also very significant differences in performing accounting for a security in receivership or a corporation or even a trust. I try to perform all the duties that I am APPOINTED to do, but this one is quite the challenge.&#xA;So I have a better idea. Let&amp;rsquo;s have an interactive thread on strictly ACCOUNTING. Ask your questions here and I will try to show you what the answers are and how you can verify them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Be a Plumber</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/how-to-be-a-plumber/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/how-to-be-a-plumber/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;By: Chris Schulte&#xA;CC BY-ND-NC 3.0 UNPORTED LICENSE&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How to be a plumber, appointed by Ricky South&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Step one is to actually know what the fuck you are doing. There is schooling involved, trade hours, etc. [someone remind me to get back to the schooling part later please]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Step 2-4: boring plumber shit.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Step 5: what to do with the ACCOUNTING!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you work 5 days a week at $90 an hour, this should bring you in about $150k per year in labor, then maybe a little more if you mark up parts. There are expenses tied to this REVENUE that can be legally accounted against this to determine INCOME. But there&amp;rsquo;s a tax on this shit, so legally, you would want INCOME to be the lowest it could be while having enough to cover personal expenses, etc. so what options do you have?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Say That You Are 18</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/lets-say-that-you-are-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/lets-say-that-you-are-18/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ive been hinting at something in here for months, so now I will go into detail using a totally metaphorical and totally not real example. 😁&#xA;Let&amp;rsquo;s say that you are 18 and you are smarter than the rest of your high school buddies, so you opt to go to trade school rather than college. This is a GOOD DECISION! You figure that you can work as an apprentice during the day to collect your hours and go to school at night to satisfy the classroom requirements for the license that you hope to earn (yes, this is hilarious). Does everyone know how this very simple mechanism works? &amp;hellip;.good.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Robbing a bank&#39;</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/robbing-a-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/robbing-a-bank/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ok, since there are no questions on the board, I guess everyone is on the same page here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lets discuss robbing a bank. 😀&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This post is appointed by Neens Jean. She thinks wrong and values the wrong things, but she really means to appoint this article.&#xA;You found some stranger on the internet who calls you a worthless sack of shit, but you read and what he says makes sense. How can the two points be right? Is he wrong? Well, lets find out. You are all &amp;ldquo;employees&amp;rdquo; who earn a living using this legal status. This means that you are using a security in receivership to, presumably, earn income. This is a worthless legal status because you will never gain. The administrators of the receivership will surely limit how well you do and make sure they do much better off of the deal of you working. So you are worthless. How do we steal back?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
