<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>#Jurisdiction on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/%23jurisdiction/</link>
    <description>Recent content in #Jurisdiction on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/%23jurisdiction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Those Who Mistrust</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/those-who-mis-trust/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/those-who-mis-trust/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The title of this paper is a little tricky. We’ll just clarify at the outset that those who mistrust— miss trusts. Those who mistrust are those who make a serious mistake. What I will be discussing is the mistake of missing the point about Express Trusts and the advantages of using Express Trusts wisely.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To illustrate I will tell you about a peculiar case I worked on in 2002 with an attorney who contacted me on a recommendation from the attorney who I actually assisted in some litigation against one of that attorney’s former clients. The case was interesting because it was one of those situations I had come to appreciate: someone puts all the protections in place before the problems start, instead of scrambling to try to fix a problem at a time when they should’ve had the protections in place already.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trustees In Commerce: A Way of Life</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/trustees-in-commerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/trustees-in-commerce/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, take all that and place a simple barrier between the &amp;ldquo;sovereign&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;secured party&amp;rdquo; and commerce. The barrier is called an&#xA;Express Trust under the Common Law. Throw out the fragile sovereign crown andgive the man a bulletproof trustee helmet. Now, instead of him owning a plot of land with a castle, havinga royal army and a royal staff of workers, stockpiling his own weapons, having Federal Reserve Notes orminted coins in his personal possession, and understanding all applicable bodies of law to protecthimself— he now does these things on behalf of a trust. Problem solved.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGENCY (ARTIFICIAL PERSONS) FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/agency-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/agency-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: AGENCY (ARTIFICIAL PERSONS) FOR IDIOTS (c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;HER MAJESTY AND AN ORGANIZATION.  It’s the ultimate artificial person.  To understand what this means you should refer to my earlier articles.  The Criminal Code of Canada states, inter alia [Source R.S., c. C-34, s. 2 “INTERPRETATION”]:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“every one”, “person” and “owner”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;« quiconque », « individu », « personne » et « propriétaire »&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
