<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>#RegisteredAgentsActAsCurrencyExchanges on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/%23registeredagentsactascurrencyexchanges/</link>
    <description>Recent content in #RegisteredAgentsActAsCurrencyExchanges on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/%23registeredagentsactascurrencyexchanges/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Say That You Are 18</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/lets-say-that-you-are-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/lets-say-that-you-are-18/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ive been hinting at something in here for months, so now I will go into detail using a totally metaphorical and totally not real example. 😁&#xA;Let&amp;rsquo;s say that you are 18 and you are smarter than the rest of your high school buddies, so you opt to go to trade school rather than college. This is a GOOD DECISION! You figure that you can work as an apprentice during the day to collect your hours and go to school at night to satisfy the classroom requirements for the license that you hope to earn (yes, this is hilarious). Does everyone know how this very simple mechanism works? &amp;hellip;.good.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PERSONS FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/persons-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/persons-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: PERSONS FOR IDIOTS (c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All of you reading have, at one point or another, encountered the term “PERSON”.  After very little investigation, you are forced to accept the realization that you are not a PERSON, rather you HAVE a PERSON. This distinction is the first “lie of ommission” that you will encounter in the world of the “LEGAL”. THE TENDER FOR LAW axiom “LEGAL=SURETY AND ACCOUNTING” makes navigating “law” a lot simpler, and it’s very easy to spot the lies of ommission/ambiguity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AGENCY (ARTIFICIAL PERSONS) FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/agency-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/agency-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: AGENCY (ARTIFICIAL PERSONS) FOR IDIOTS (c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;HER MAJESTY AND AN ORGANIZATION.  It’s the ultimate artificial person.  To understand what this means you should refer to my earlier articles.  The Criminal Code of Canada states, inter alia [Source R.S., c. C-34, s. 2 “INTERPRETATION”]:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“every one”, “person” and “owner”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;« quiconque », « individu », « personne » et « propriétaire »&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Show Me The Money</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/show-me-the-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/show-me-the-money/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 id=&#34;c-ingenium-holdings-incorporated-under-a-creative-commons-30-unported-license-by-nd-nc&#34;&gt;(c) INGENIUM HOLDINGS INCORPORATED under a Creative Commons 3.0 Unported License; BY-ND-NC&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you’re like me, for most of your life you’ve had minimal conscious interactions with ACCOUNTING, It was always presented to me as something very boring and complicated so I&amp;rsquo;d always avoided learning about it. While embracing my love of ignorance &lt;strong&gt;I COULD NOT SEE&lt;/strong&gt; how this &lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACTION&lt;/strong&gt; was being used against me every day or how I could use it for my benefit.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONE PEOPLE’S PUBLIC FRAUD (OPPF) Part TWO: The UCC For Idiots</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/oppf-p2-ucc-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/oppf-p2-ucc-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;one-peoples-public-fraud-oppf-part-two-the-ucc-for-idiots&#34;&gt;ONE PEOPLE’S PUBLIC FRAUD (OPPF) Part TWO: The UCC For Idiots&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ORIGINALLY PUBLISHED on 24 February 2013 · in THE TENDER FOR LAW: ONE PEOPLE’S PUBLIC FRAUD (OPPF) Part TWO: The UCC for Idiots (c) 2013 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&#xA;As promised, I am now going to cover the UNIFORM COMMERCIAL CODE (or UCC, for you idiots who type with your thumbs.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;FUCK! Myths about THIS shit, sure has “done the rounds”, hasn’t it? No more myths have been generated, out of a piece of regulation, than the UNIFORM COMMERCIAL CODE!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
