<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TRUSTS on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/categories/trusts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in TRUSTS on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/categories/trusts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Those Who Mistrust</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/those-who-mis-trust/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/those-who-mis-trust/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The title of this paper is a little tricky. We’ll just clarify at the outset that those who mistrust— miss trusts. Those who mistrust are those who make a serious mistake. What I will be discussing is the mistake of missing the point about Express Trusts and the advantages of using Express Trusts wisely.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To illustrate I will tell you about a peculiar case I worked on in 2002 with an attorney who contacted me on a recommendation from the attorney who I actually assisted in some litigation against one of that attorney’s former clients. The case was interesting because it was one of those situations I had come to appreciate: someone puts all the protections in place before the problems start, instead of scrambling to try to fix a problem at a time when they should’ve had the protections in place already.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trustees In Commerce: A Way of Life</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/trustees-in-commerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/trustees-in-commerce/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, take all that and place a simple barrier between the &amp;ldquo;sovereign&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;secured party&amp;rdquo; and commerce. The barrier is called an&#xA;Express Trust under the Common Law. Throw out the fragile sovereign crown andgive the man a bulletproof trustee helmet. Now, instead of him owning a plot of land with a castle, havinga royal army and a royal staff of workers, stockpiling his own weapons, having Federal Reserve Notes orminted coins in his personal possession, and understanding all applicable bodies of law to protecthimself— he now does these things on behalf of a trust. Problem solved.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROPER NOTICE FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/proper-notice-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/proper-notice-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW – LIVE EXAMPLE #001 – PROPER NOTICE FOR IDIOTS (c) 2013 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&#xA;TONIGHT’S TOPIC: PROPER NOTICE&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In one of the many ongoing AQUILAE initiatives, I have cause to produce a NOTICE.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since I’m using THE TENDER FOR LAW as a notebook for my students, I figure I might as well “kill two birds with one stone” by discussing the aspects of NOTICE here, more specifically PROPER NOTICE.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE TENDER FOR LAW: The Looming Threat Of FreeDumb – ADDENDUM</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/the-looming-threat-of-freedumb-addendum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/the-looming-threat-of-freedumb-addendum/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: The Looming Threat of FreeDumb – ADDENDUM (c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License. ADDENDUM TO [ https://www.facebook.com/notes/scott-duncan/the-tender-for-law-the-looming-threat-of-freedumb/815869621812845 ]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I received a message from a woman today that filled me with both anger and despair.  As you may have guessed, I justifiably hold all of you in the highest contempt.  Often I find myself longing for the mindset and ethical structure (or lack thereof) that would allow me to take my many extraordinary abilities, and just kill you all.  I won’t lie to you…it’s not for your safety, it’s for mine.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONE PEOPLE’S PUBLIC FRAUD (OPPF) Part TWO: The UCC For Idiots</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/oppf-p2-ucc-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Feb 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/oppf-p2-ucc-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;one-peoples-public-fraud-oppf-part-two-the-ucc-for-idiots&#34;&gt;ONE PEOPLE’S PUBLIC FRAUD (OPPF) Part TWO: The UCC For Idiots&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ORIGINALLY PUBLISHED on 24 February 2013 · in THE TENDER FOR LAW: ONE PEOPLE’S PUBLIC FRAUD (OPPF) Part TWO: The UCC for Idiots (c) 2013 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&#xA;As promised, I am now going to cover the UNIFORM COMMERCIAL CODE (or UCC, for you idiots who type with your thumbs.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;FUCK! Myths about THIS shit, sure has “done the rounds”, hasn’t it? No more myths have been generated, out of a piece of regulation, than the UNIFORM COMMERCIAL CODE!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
