<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>#AllBeliefIsEvil on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/%23allbeliefisevil/</link>
    <description>Recent content in #AllBeliefIsEvil on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/%23allbeliefisevil/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Trust But Verify</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/trust-but-verify/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/trust-but-verify/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Scott always said to us: &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t know what you don&amp;rsquo;t know&amp;rdquo;. I now see how true this is. He always said too: &amp;ldquo;I can&amp;rsquo;t dumb it down any further, you have to meet me in the middle.&amp;rdquo; The 2 things are true. The reason it can&amp;rsquo;t be dumbed down any further is because of the language. The language of the Angols (English) was stolen from you and forked to legalese. It&amp;rsquo;s a bastardized form of English that doesn&amp;rsquo;t use synonyms or homonyms. Each term has 1 meaning. Anthony Massoli has posted from his notes, the most obvious of these. The one I&amp;rsquo;ve found that is most different is transportation. Alan Day is a direct descendant of the people affected by this.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hero&#39;s Journey</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/hero-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/hero-journey/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;every-one-lives-out-a-myth-and-you-should-know-what-your-myth-is-because-maybe-its-a-tragedy&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;Every one lives out a myth, and you should know what your myth is because maybe it&amp;rsquo;s a tragedy&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jews stole your birthright, now there’s only ritual without reflection.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hero&#39;s_journey&#34;&gt;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hero&amp;rsquo;s_journey&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The point of the Hero’s Story is to discover who One could become. One goes in[put] and comes out[put] transformed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 id=&#34;you-dont-know-who-you-are&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;You don&amp;rsquo;t know who you are&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;-Scott Duncan&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most of us don&amp;rsquo;t even start the journey, or use a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/j/journal.asp&#34;&gt;journal&lt;/a&gt;, because belief acts as a barrier that &amp;ldquo;protects&amp;rdquo; us from the unknown. Through belief we&amp;rsquo;ve damaged the mechanism that was supposed to guide us in developing our story of turning the unknown into the known; repeatedly. The mechanism is something like: “the courageous commitment to go out [look], find what&amp;rsquo;s true, and to speak it to others so they might also choose to find it&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Prodigal Son</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/the-prodigal-son/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/the-prodigal-son/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A few words on the subject of being right.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My name is Scott Duncan.  I am trusted with a lot of secrets, and I keep those secrets by being honest.  It&amp;rsquo;s counter-intuitive, but it works profoundly well.  I write on these relatively obscure mediums which, while public, aren&amp;rsquo;t actively promoted.  This is by design.  Only those who have been following me for the past four years will truly understand what I&amp;rsquo;m saying here; and the rest of you, of course, will misinterpret it.  Know that any action that you take based on that misinterpretation, is by design.  I fully expect you to do the wrong thing, based on the wrong perception, and when you do, that makes you my servant.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Piece-of-Shit-Christians are Pieces of shit: Why Rational Discourse is Futile</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/piece-of-shit-christians-are-pieces-of-shit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/piece-of-shit-christians-are-pieces-of-shit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Did you know I&amp;rsquo;m an Ordained Minister?  It&amp;rsquo;s true.  I can legally marry people in Texas.  I&amp;rsquo;ve been to Texas twice in my life; both times I wasn&amp;rsquo;t there for more than a week.  I did, however, use my time efficiently and invested it to become an Ordained Minister of the &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;Church of the Subgenius&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt; (Praise Bob!).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Truth About The Illuminati Or Why Piece-Of-Shit Christians Are Such Pieces-Of-Shit</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/or-why-piece-of-shit-chistiansare-such-pieces-of-shit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/or-why-piece-of-shit-chistiansare-such-pieces-of-shit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Shared under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;SCOTT DUNCAN·WEDNESDAY, 21 OCTOBER 2015&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Piece-of-Shit Christians” – you hear me say it a lot. I say it so much, and I’ve been saying it for so long, that the prefix “Piece-of-Shit” is automatically inserted in front of it, each and every time I hear the word “Christian”. This is much like the experience of Elliot in “Mr. Robot” with “Evil Corp”. (I also find myself mentally apologizing to Claudia Christian every time I think of her. Shit…there I go again! Sorry Claudia. :/)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE TENDER FOR LAW: The Looming Threat Of FreeDumb – ADDENDUM</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/the-looming-threat-of-freedumb-addendum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/the-looming-threat-of-freedumb-addendum/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: The Looming Threat of FreeDumb – ADDENDUM (c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License. ADDENDUM TO [ https://www.facebook.com/notes/scott-duncan/the-tender-for-law-the-looming-threat-of-freedumb/815869621812845 ]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I received a message from a woman today that filled me with both anger and despair.  As you may have guessed, I justifiably hold all of you in the highest contempt.  Often I find myself longing for the mindset and ethical structure (or lack thereof) that would allow me to take my many extraordinary abilities, and just kill you all.  I won’t lie to you…it’s not for your safety, it’s for mine.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
