<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Accounting on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/categories/accounting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Accounting on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/categories/accounting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>An Article About Accounting</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/an-article-about-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/an-article-about-accounting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I was asked to write an article on Accounting. This is a VERY BROAD topic. There are also very significant differences in performing accounting for a security in receivership or a corporation or even a trust. I try to perform all the duties that I am APPOINTED to do, but this one is quite the challenge.&#xA;So I have a better idea. Let&amp;rsquo;s have an interactive thread on strictly ACCOUNTING. Ask your questions here and I will try to show you what the answers are and how you can verify them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Say That You Are 18</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/lets-say-that-you-are-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/lets-say-that-you-are-18/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ive been hinting at something in here for months, so now I will go into detail using a totally metaphorical and totally not real example. 😁&#xA;Let&amp;rsquo;s say that you are 18 and you are smarter than the rest of your high school buddies, so you opt to go to trade school rather than college. This is a GOOD DECISION! You figure that you can work as an apprentice during the day to collect your hours and go to school at night to satisfy the classroom requirements for the license that you hope to earn (yes, this is hilarious). Does everyone know how this very simple mechanism works? &amp;hellip;.good.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvel Jesus, Better Than Jesus, &amp; The Sermon on The Keyboard</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/marvel-jesus-better-than-jesus-and-the-sermon-on-the-keyboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/marvel-jesus-better-than-jesus-and-the-sermon-on-the-keyboard/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/bc2df4c5-c6d4-4394-9f85-b5deaf00356a&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;marvel-jesus-better-than-jesus--the-sermon-on-the-keyboard&#34;&gt;Marvel Jesus, Better Than Jesus, &amp;amp; The Sermon on The Keyboard&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Appointed by &amp;ldquo;N&amp;rdquo; for &amp;ldquo;Not Surety&amp;rdquo;,&#xA;A reference to THE TENDER FOR LAW on Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Shared under a Creative Commons 3.0 Unported License; BY-ND-NC&#xA;(c) INGENIUM HOLDINGS INCORPORATED&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I promised to handle this “thing” with the greatest care, so &amp;ldquo;what is it?&amp;rdquo; you might ask, how did I become a holder of it, and what does this stewardship mean? What does accounting have to do with the “Kingdom of God”?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SURETY FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/surety-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/surety-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW – SURETY FOR IDIOTS (c) 2013 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It’s been a while since I’ve posted an article, and I’ve solidified the “For Idiots” concept. Let’s cover SURETY!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One of the most painful things about being on FaceBook is having to endure the fact that people with chronic Dunning–Kruger effect still think that their ignorance has the same standing as my knowledge; and they will happily state many unkind things regarding my character when I challenge their “pulled-out-of-their-ass” mythology.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Is The Difference Between LEGAL And LAWFUL?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/what-is-the-diffrence-between-legal-and-lawful/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/what-is-the-diffrence-between-legal-and-lawful/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What is the difference between LEGAL and LAWFUL?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To answer this question one must first answer the question, “What is LAW?”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Social conditioning and the public discourse of lawyers is intentionally designed to stop you from asking this question.  Here in reality there have been many attempts to define it.  Law is just a weasel-word catch-phrase, like “Due Process“. It doesn’t actually exist.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Show Me The Money</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/show-me-the-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/show-me-the-money/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 id=&#34;c-ingenium-holdings-incorporated-under-a-creative-commons-30-unported-license-by-nd-nc&#34;&gt;(c) INGENIUM HOLDINGS INCORPORATED under a Creative Commons 3.0 Unported License; BY-ND-NC&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you’re like me, for most of your life you’ve had minimal conscious interactions with ACCOUNTING, It was always presented to me as something very boring and complicated so I&amp;rsquo;d always avoided learning about it. While embracing my love of ignorance &lt;strong&gt;I COULD NOT SEE&lt;/strong&gt; how this &lt;strong&gt;ABSTRACTION&lt;/strong&gt; was being used against me every day or how I could use it for my benefit.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hero&#39;s Journey</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/hero-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/hero-journey/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;every-one-lives-out-a-myth-and-you-should-know-what-your-myth-is-because-maybe-its-a-tragedy&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;Every one lives out a myth, and you should know what your myth is because maybe it&amp;rsquo;s a tragedy&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jews stole your birthright, now there’s only ritual without reflection.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hero&#39;s_journey&#34;&gt;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hero&amp;rsquo;s_journey&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The point of the Hero’s Story is to discover who One could become. One goes in[put] and comes out[put] transformed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 id=&#34;you-dont-know-who-you-are&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;You don&amp;rsquo;t know who you are&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;-Scott Duncan&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most of us don&amp;rsquo;t even start the journey, or use a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/j/journal.asp&#34;&gt;journal&lt;/a&gt;, because belief acts as a barrier that &amp;ldquo;protects&amp;rdquo; us from the unknown. Through belief we&amp;rsquo;ve damaged the mechanism that was supposed to guide us in developing our story of turning the unknown into the known; repeatedly. The mechanism is something like: “the courageous commitment to go out [look], find what&amp;rsquo;s true, and to speak it to others so they might also choose to find it&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hate Speech</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/hate-speech/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/hate-speech/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The title of this article is not just a title, it&amp;rsquo;s intent.  By intent, I mean that I intend to make this article qualify as &amp;ldquo;hate speech&amp;rdquo; according to every Western Law on the books.  That&amp;rsquo;s right, I intend to commit the &amp;ldquo;crime&amp;rdquo; of &amp;ldquo;hate speech&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Hate speech&amp;rdquo; is one of the invented crimes of the 1970&amp;rsquo;s.  It is one of the many LEGAL mechanisms used to suspend your critical thought.  Legally, &amp;ldquo;hate speech&amp;rdquo; is defined, but &amp;ldquo;hate&amp;rdquo; itself is not legally defined.  There&amp;rsquo;s a reason for this.  If &amp;ldquo;hate&amp;rdquo; were legally defined, even the most dull-witted reader would realize that any legislation that bore this definition, would literally be criminalizing an emotion.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paperwork Terroism!</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/paperwork-terrorism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/paperwork-terrorism/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t know if any of you have read this bill, C-16, and the terrifying ramifications contained therein; but if you haven&amp;rsquo;t you really should, even if you&amp;rsquo;re not in Canada.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As this &amp;ldquo;law&amp;rdquo; is currently framed, my satirical recreation of a &amp;ldquo;Gender Fluid&amp;rdquo; PSA would be a crime in Canada, for which I could be jailed.  If you think I&amp;rsquo;m being alarmist, I remind you that people have been sentenced to multiple years in prison, simply for publishing the INTENT to publish, a book questioning the Holocaust.  This happens in Germany right now.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
