<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>#WhoAmI on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/%23whoami/</link>
    <description>Recent content in #WhoAmI on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/%23whoami/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>An Article About Accounting</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/an-article-about-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/an-article-about-accounting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I was asked to write an article on Accounting. This is a VERY BROAD topic. There are also very significant differences in performing accounting for a security in receivership or a corporation or even a trust. I try to perform all the duties that I am APPOINTED to do, but this one is quite the challenge.&#xA;So I have a better idea. Let&amp;rsquo;s have an interactive thread on strictly ACCOUNTING. Ask your questions here and I will try to show you what the answers are and how you can verify them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PERSONS FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/persons-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/persons-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: PERSONS FOR IDIOTS (c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All of you reading have, at one point or another, encountered the term “PERSON”.  After very little investigation, you are forced to accept the realization that you are not a PERSON, rather you HAVE a PERSON. This distinction is the first “lie of ommission” that you will encounter in the world of the “LEGAL”. THE TENDER FOR LAW axiom “LEGAL=SURETY AND ACCOUNTING” makes navigating “law” a lot simpler, and it’s very easy to spot the lies of ommission/ambiguity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who’s On First: FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/whos-on-first-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/whos-on-first-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h5 id=&#34;whos-on-first-for-idiots-c-2015-roguesupport-inc-under-a-creative-commons-attribution-noncommercial-noderivs-30-unported-license&#34;&gt;Who’s On First: FOR IDIOTS (c) 2015 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For anyone still lagging behind in the “name game” confusion surrounding systems relating to law and money, I present, “Who’s on First?”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also for your edification, I have copied/pasted the opening sentences from Wikipedia describing the comedy routine, below:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Who’s on First?” is descended from turn-of-the-century burlesque sketches that used plays on words and names. Examples are “The Baker Scene” (the shop is located on Watt Street) and “Who Dyed” (the owner is named Who). In the 1930 movie Cracked Nuts, comedians Bert Wheeler and Robert Woolsey examine a map of a mythical kingdom with dialogue like this: “What is next to Which.” “What is the name of the town next to Which?” “Yes.” In English music halls (Britain’s equivalent of vaudeville theaters), comedian Will Hay performed a routine in the early 1930s (and possibly earlier) as a schoolmaster interviewing a schoolboy named Howe who came from Ware but now lives in Wye. By the early 1930s, a “Baseball Routine” had become a standard bit for burlesque comics across the United States. Abbott’s wife recalled Bud performing the routine with another comedian before teaming with Costello.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marvel Jesus, Better Than Jesus, &amp; The Sermon on The Keyboard</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/marvel-jesus-better-than-jesus-and-the-sermon-on-the-keyboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/marvel-jesus-better-than-jesus-and-the-sermon-on-the-keyboard/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://github.com/user-attachments/assets/bc2df4c5-c6d4-4394-9f85-b5deaf00356a&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;marvel-jesus-better-than-jesus--the-sermon-on-the-keyboard&#34;&gt;Marvel Jesus, Better Than Jesus, &amp;amp; The Sermon on The Keyboard&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Appointed by &amp;ldquo;N&amp;rdquo; for &amp;ldquo;Not Surety&amp;rdquo;,&#xA;A reference to THE TENDER FOR LAW on Facebook.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Shared under a Creative Commons 3.0 Unported License; BY-ND-NC&#xA;(c) INGENIUM HOLDINGS INCORPORATED&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I promised to handle this “thing” with the greatest care, so &amp;ldquo;what is it?&amp;rdquo; you might ask, how did I become a holder of it, and what does this stewardship mean? What does accounting have to do with the “Kingdom of God”?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROPER NOTICE FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/proper-notice-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/proper-notice-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW – LIVE EXAMPLE #001 – PROPER NOTICE FOR IDIOTS (c) 2013 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&#xA;TONIGHT’S TOPIC: PROPER NOTICE&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In one of the many ongoing AQUILAE initiatives, I have cause to produce a NOTICE.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since I’m using THE TENDER FOR LAW as a notebook for my students, I figure I might as well “kill two birds with one stone” by discussing the aspects of NOTICE here, more specifically PROPER NOTICE.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Is The Difference Between LEGAL And LAWFUL?</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/what-is-the-diffrence-between-legal-and-lawful/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/what-is-the-diffrence-between-legal-and-lawful/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What is the difference between LEGAL and LAWFUL?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To answer this question one must first answer the question, “What is LAW?”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Social conditioning and the public discourse of lawyers is intentionally designed to stop you from asking this question.  Here in reality there have been many attempts to define it.  Law is just a weasel-word catch-phrase, like “Due Process“. It doesn’t actually exist.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hero&#39;s Journey</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/hero-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/hero-journey/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;every-one-lives-out-a-myth-and-you-should-know-what-your-myth-is-because-maybe-its-a-tragedy&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;Every one lives out a myth, and you should know what your myth is because maybe it&amp;rsquo;s a tragedy&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jews stole your birthright, now there’s only ritual without reflection.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hero&#39;s_journey&#34;&gt;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hero&amp;rsquo;s_journey&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The point of the Hero’s Story is to discover who One could become. One goes in[put] and comes out[put] transformed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 id=&#34;you-dont-know-who-you-are&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;You don&amp;rsquo;t know who you are&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;-Scott Duncan&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most of us don&amp;rsquo;t even start the journey, or use a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/j/journal.asp&#34;&gt;journal&lt;/a&gt;, because belief acts as a barrier that &amp;ldquo;protects&amp;rdquo; us from the unknown. Through belief we&amp;rsquo;ve damaged the mechanism that was supposed to guide us in developing our story of turning the unknown into the known; repeatedly. The mechanism is something like: “the courageous commitment to go out [look], find what&amp;rsquo;s true, and to speak it to others so they might also choose to find it&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Truth About The Illuminati Or Why Piece-Of-Shit Christians Are Such Pieces-Of-Shit</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/or-why-piece-of-shit-chistiansare-such-pieces-of-shit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/or-why-piece-of-shit-chistiansare-such-pieces-of-shit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Shared under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;SCOTT DUNCAN·WEDNESDAY, 21 OCTOBER 2015&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“Piece-of-Shit Christians” – you hear me say it a lot. I say it so much, and I’ve been saying it for so long, that the prefix “Piece-of-Shit” is automatically inserted in front of it, each and every time I hear the word “Christian”. This is much like the experience of Elliot in “Mr. Robot” with “Evil Corp”. (I also find myself mentally apologizing to Claudia Christian every time I think of her. Shit…there I go again! Sorry Claudia. :/)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
