<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Narrative on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/categories/narrative/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Narrative on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/categories/narrative/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>An Article About Accounting</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/an-article-about-accounting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/an-article-about-accounting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I was asked to write an article on Accounting. This is a VERY BROAD topic. There are also very significant differences in performing accounting for a security in receivership or a corporation or even a trust. I try to perform all the duties that I am APPOINTED to do, but this one is quite the challenge.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So I have a better idea. Let&amp;rsquo;s have an interactive thread on strictly ACCOUNTING. Ask your questions here and I will try to show you what the answers are and how you can verify them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Say That You Are 18</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/lets-say-that-you-are-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/lets-say-that-you-are-18/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ive been hinting at something in here for months, so now I will go into detail using a totally metaphorical and totally not real example. 😁&#xA;Let&amp;rsquo;s say that you are 18 and you are smarter than the rest of your high school buddies, so you opt to go to trade school rather than college. This is a GOOD DECISION! You figure that you can work as an apprentice during the day to collect your hours and go to school at night to satisfy the classroom requirements for the license that you hope to earn (yes, this is hilarious). Does everyone know how this very simple mechanism works? &amp;hellip;.good.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#39;Robbing a bank&#39;</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/robbing-a-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/chris-schulte/robbing-a-bank/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ok, since there are no questions on the board, I guess everyone is on the same page here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lets discuss robbing a bank. 😀&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This post is appointed by Neens Jean. She thinks wrong and values the wrong things, but she really means to appoint this article.&#xA;You found some stranger on the internet who calls you a worthless sack of shit, but you read and what he says makes sense. How can the two points be right? Is he wrong? Well, lets find out. You are all &amp;ldquo;employees&amp;rdquo; who earn a living using this legal status. This means that you are using a security in receivership to, presumably, earn income. This is a worthless legal status because you will never gain. The administrators of the receivership will surely limit how well you do and make sure they do much better off of the deal of you working. So you are worthless. How do we steal back?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Hero&#39;s Journey</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/hero-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/various-authors/hero-journey/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;every-one-lives-out-a-myth-and-you-should-know-what-your-myth-is-because-maybe-its-a-tragedy&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;Every one lives out a myth, and you should know what your myth is because maybe it&amp;rsquo;s a tragedy&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jews stole your birthright, now there’s only ritual without reflection.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hero&#39;s_journey&#34;&gt;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hero&amp;rsquo;s_journey&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The point of the Hero’s Story is to discover who One could become. One goes in[put] and comes out[put] transformed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h5 id=&#34;you-dont-know-who-you-are&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;You don&amp;rsquo;t know who you are&amp;rdquo;&lt;/h5&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;-Scott Duncan&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most of us don&amp;rsquo;t even start the journey, or use a &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.investopedia.com/terms/j/journal.asp&#34;&gt;journal&lt;/a&gt;, because belief acts as a barrier that &amp;ldquo;protects&amp;rdquo; us from the unknown. Through belief we&amp;rsquo;ve damaged the mechanism that was supposed to guide us in developing our story of turning the unknown into the known; repeatedly. The mechanism is something like: “the courageous commitment to go out [look], find what&amp;rsquo;s true, and to speak it to others so they might also choose to find it&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Prodigal Son</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/the-prodigal-son/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/the-prodigal-son/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A few words on the subject of being right.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My name is Scott Duncan.  I am trusted with a lot of secrets, and I keep those secrets by being honest.  It&amp;rsquo;s counter-intuitive, but it works profoundly well.  I write on these relatively obscure mediums which, while public, aren&amp;rsquo;t actively promoted.  This is by design.  Only those who have been following me for the past four years will truly understand what I&amp;rsquo;m saying here; and the rest of you, of course, will misinterpret it.  Know that any action that you take based on that misinterpretation, is by design.  I fully expect you to do the wrong thing, based on the wrong perception, and when you do, that makes you my servant.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paperwork Terroism!</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/paperwork-terrorism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/paperwork-terrorism/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t know if any of you have read this bill, C-16, and the terrifying ramifications contained therein; but if you haven&amp;rsquo;t you really should, even if you&amp;rsquo;re not in Canada.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As this &amp;ldquo;law&amp;rdquo; is currently framed, my satirical recreation of a &amp;ldquo;Gender Fluid&amp;rdquo; PSA would be a crime in Canada, for which I could be jailed.  If you think I&amp;rsquo;m being alarmist, I remind you that people have been sentenced to multiple years in prison, simply for publishing the INTENT to publish, a book questioning the Holocaust.  This happens in Germany right now.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE TENDER FOR LAW: The Looming Threat Of FreeDumb – ADDENDUM</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/the-looming-threat-of-freedumb-addendum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/the-looming-threat-of-freedumb-addendum/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: The Looming Threat of FreeDumb – ADDENDUM (c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License. ADDENDUM TO [ https://www.facebook.com/notes/scott-duncan/the-tender-for-law-the-looming-threat-of-freedumb/815869621812845 ]&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I received a message from a woman today that filled me with both anger and despair.  As you may have guessed, I justifiably hold all of you in the highest contempt.  Often I find myself longing for the mindset and ethical structure (or lack thereof) that would allow me to take my many extraordinary abilities, and just kill you all.  I won’t lie to you…it’s not for your safety, it’s for mine.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
