<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HER MAJESTY and an ORGANIZATION on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/categories/her-majesty-and-an-organization/</link>
    <description>Recent content in HER MAJESTY and an ORGANIZATION on TheTenderForLaw.com Test Deployment</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/categories/her-majesty-and-an-organization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PERSONS FOR IDIOTS</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/persons-for-idiots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/persons-for-idiots/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;THE TENDER FOR LAW: PERSONS FOR IDIOTS (c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All of you reading have, at one point or another, encountered the term “PERSON”.  After very little investigation, you are forced to accept the realization that you are not a PERSON, rather you HAVE a PERSON. This distinction is the first “lie of ommission” that you will encounter in the world of the “LEGAL”. THE TENDER FOR LAW axiom “LEGAL=SURETY AND ACCOUNTING” makes navigating “law” a lot simpler, and it’s very easy to spot the lies of ommission/ambiguity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE TENDER FOR LAW: The Looming Threat Of FreeDumb</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/the-looming-threat-of-freedumb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/articles/scott-duncan/the-looming-threat-of-freedumb/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Looming Threat of FreeDumb (c) 2014 ROGUESUPPORT INC. under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-NoDerivs 3.0 Unported License.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this writing I shall go further into my Noble Title, the Trust I commissioned in 1982, the Constitution, and the term ‘Freeman’.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My grandfather (John Clark Duncan) was an extraordinary man.  He was of Noble descent, and served the Royal House of Windsor in World War II, training fighter pilots and later joining the 435/436 Burma Star Squadron; where he was remembered for saving a bunch of people’s asses  (and giving somebody else the credit), and depth-charging a whale off the coast of Vancouver island.Most people are unaware of the events of 1933 and the Treaty of Westminster, a long dry, boring, convoluted document that released the subjects of the Monarchy, demoted Nobles to the status of Subject, and made all of their descendants, and current “Subjects”, Freemen.  The remaining bills granting that status were signed by John Diefenbaker in 1960, and here’s where the legal shell game begins.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
